<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Workbook xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:spreadsheet"
 xmlns:o="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office"
 xmlns:x="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:excel"
 xmlns:ss="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:spreadsheet"
 xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/TR/REC-html40">
 <DocumentProperties xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office">
  <Author>Sadie Roosa</Author>
  <LastAuthor>Sadie Roosa</LastAuthor>
  <Created>2014-11-06T16:52:44Z</Created>
  <LastSaved>2015-01-06T20:25:33Z</LastSaved>
  <Company>WGBH</Company>
  <Version>14.0</Version>
 </DocumentProperties>
 <OfficeDocumentSettings xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office">
  <AllowPNG/>
 </OfficeDocumentSettings>
 <ExcelWorkbook xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:excel">
  <WindowHeight>13160</WindowHeight>
  <WindowWidth>32420</WindowWidth>
  <WindowTopX>120</WindowTopX>
  <WindowTopY>0</WindowTopY>
  <ProtectStructure>False</ProtectStructure>
  <ProtectWindows>False</ProtectWindows>
 </ExcelWorkbook>
 <Styles>
  <Style ss:ID="Default" ss:Name="Normal">
   <Alignment ss:Vertical="Bottom"/>
   <Borders/>
   <Font ss:FontName="Calibri" x:Family="Swiss" ss:Size="12" ss:Color="#000000"/>
   <Interior/>
   <NumberFormat/>
   <Protection/>
  </Style>
  <Style ss:ID="s257">
   <Alignment ss:Vertical="Bottom" ss:WrapText="1"/>
  </Style>
  <Style ss:ID="s258">
   <Font ss:FontName="Calibri" ss:Size="12"/>
   <NumberFormat ss:Format="@"/>
  </Style>
  <Style ss:ID="s259">
   <Alignment ss:Vertical="Bottom"/>
   <Font ss:FontName="Calibri" x:Family="Swiss" ss:Size="12" ss:Color="#000000"
    ss:Bold="1"/>
  </Style>
  <Style ss:ID="s260">
   <Alignment ss:Vertical="Bottom"/>
   <Font ss:FontName="Calibri" ss:Size="12"/>
   <NumberFormat ss:Format="@"/>
  </Style>
  <Style ss:ID="s261">
   <Alignment ss:Vertical="Bottom"/>
  </Style>
 </Styles>
 <Worksheet ss:Name="Data">
  <Table ss:ExpandedColumnCount="10" ss:ExpandedRowCount="125" x:FullColumns="1"
   x:FullRows="1" ss:StyleID="s261" ss:DefaultColumnWidth="65"
   ss:DefaultRowHeight="15">
   <Column ss:StyleID="s261" ss:AutoFitWidth="0" ss:Width="344"/>
   <Column ss:StyleID="s260" ss:AutoFitWidth="0" ss:Width="135"/>
   <Column ss:StyleID="s261" ss:AutoFitWidth="0" ss:Width="344"/>
   <Column ss:StyleID="s261" ss:AutoFitWidth="0" ss:Width="127"/>
   <Column ss:StyleID="s261" ss:AutoFitWidth="0" ss:Width="115"/>
   <Column ss:StyleID="s261" ss:AutoFitWidth="0" ss:Width="220"/>
   <Column ss:StyleID="s261" ss:AutoFitWidth="0" ss:Width="395"/>
   <Column ss:StyleID="s261" ss:AutoFitWidth="0" ss:Width="363"/>
   <Column ss:StyleID="s261" ss:AutoFitWidth="0" ss:Width="99"/>
   <Row ss:StyleID="s259">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">value from pbcoreAnnotation @annotationType=&quot;organization&quot;</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s260"><Data ss:Type="String">AMS_CPB_id</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Full Display Name</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">State</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">City</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Website url</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">history of station</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">significant productions</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">logo filename</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Notes</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Illinois Public Media  (WILL)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1760</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WILL Illinois Public Media</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Illinois</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Urbana</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://will.illinois.edu/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Louisiana Public Broadcasting</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1777</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Louisiana Public Broadcasting</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Louisiana</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Baton Rouge</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.lpb.org</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">On September 6, 1975 at 11:58 a.m., longtime public television advocate Lucille Woodard flipped a ceremonial switch to sign WLPB on in Baton Rouge. It was the culmination of three years of hard work after the Legislature approved the creation of the Louisiana Educational Television Authority. &#13;Woodard, a professor at LSU, started working in the 1950s to get educational television throughout the state. After decades of frustrated efforts, the Louisiana Educational Television Authority was created in 1971 and the money to start the state network was appropriated. &#13;KLTM-TV in Monroe was the second LPB station to go on the air in 1976, followed by KLTS in Shreveport and KLPB in Lafayette in 1978. KLTL in Lake Charles signed on in 1981 and KLPA-TV in Alexandria went on the air in 1983. LPB has also entered into a partnership with WLAE-TV32 in New Orleans, which gives LPB a presence in the Crescent City.&#13;Louisiana: The State We’re In was started in 1976 with current Executive Director/CEO Beth Courtney as host and producer. The only statewide magazine in Louisiana, it has garnered many journalism and public affairs awards during its 38-year history. &#13;Our first nationally–syndicated show was Justin Wilson’s Louisiana Cooking.  Our 13th series with Chef John Folse, Hook Lies and Alibis, premieres in 2015.&#13;Documentaries about Louisiana and its “unique” politics have always been a major part of LPB’s locally produced programming. LPB combined with rising filmmaker Ken Burns (The Civil War) to produce Huey Long. Other award-winning documentaries produced or co-produced by LPB have included Uncle Earl and Lindy Boggs: Steel &amp; Velvet.&#13;The six-part series Louisiana: A History, LPB’s biggest and most lauded project to date, premiered in September 2003 to coincide with the 200th anniversary of the Louisiana Purchase. &#13;Preserving and showcasing our state’s history has always been a goal for LPB. Documentaries such as Signpost to Freedom: The 1953 Baton Rouge Bus Boycott and Against the Tide: The Story of the Cajun People of Louisiana have all explored little-known aspects of our past and present. &#13;In the 1990s, LPB produced a wide range of documentaries about our state’s artists, including Ernest Gaines: Louisiana Stories, Frame After Frame: The Images of Herman Leonard, and Kate Chopin: A Re-Awakening.&#13;When Hurricanes Katrina and Rita devastated South Louisiana and New Orleans, LPB documented the heroic actions of rescuers through Katrina’s Smallest Victims and the stories of the storm survivors trying to put the lives back together in American Creole and Washing Away: Losing Louisiana.&#13;LPB has continued to turn out award-winning documentaries. In 2012 the network was chosen by to create the official documentary for the state’s 200th anniversary of joining the Union, Louisiana: 200 Years of Statehood.  When a program was needed to kick off the Year of Music in 2013, LPB joined forces with the Lt. Governor’s Office and Harry Connick, Jr. to create Sunshine By the Stars: Celebrating Louisiana Music. It featured an all-star lineup of Louisiana musicians performing their unique versions of one of Louisiana’s State Songs “You Are My Sunshine.” </Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Louisiana: The State We’re In – Louisiana’s only statewide newsmagazine, now in its 38th season.  It started in November 1976, a little over a year after LPB went on the air. &#13;A Taste of Louisiana with Chef John Folse – Our longest running cooking show.  It started in 1990.  We’ll be airing the 13th season next year. &#13;Louisiana: A History – A six-part series produced for the 200th anniversary of the Louisiana Purchase in 2003. &#13;Sunshine By The Stars: Celebrating Louisiana’s Music – We had famous Louisiana musicians cover one of our state songs “You Are My Sunshine” in their own styles.  The song was written by our two-term Governor Jimmie Davis. &#13;Alive! In America’s Delta – a six-part wildlife documentary series. </Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LPB_logo.jpg</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUHF-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">1627</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUHF-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Texas</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Houston</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.houstonpublicmedia.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Vegas PBS (KLVX)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">1806</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Vegas PBS</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Nevada</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Las Vegas</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.vegaspbs.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WCTE</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">1864</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WCTE</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Tennessee</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Cookeville</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.wcte.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KEXP-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1658.2</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KEXP-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Washington</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Seattle</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.kexp.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WYSO-FM (WYSO Public Radio)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1570</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WYSO Public Radio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Ohio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Yellow Springs</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://wyso.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Pacifica Radio Archives</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NCSG43</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Pacifica Radio Archives</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">California</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">North Hollywood</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.pacificaradioarchives.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Wisconsin Public Television (WHA-TV)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1896</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Wisconsin Public Television</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Wisconsin</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Madison</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://wpt.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Wisconsin Public Radio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1896.2</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Wisconsin Public Radio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Wisconsin</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Madison</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.wpr.org/</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Wisconsin Public Radio is a 3-network, 34-startion regional group with a very long history.  Regular broadcasts began from our flagship station WHA (then the callsign was 9XM) before America's entry into World War I.  Our website has a nice list of our [accomplishments][http://www.wpr.org/wprs-tradition-innovation].</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Chapter A Day - one of the longest-running programs in radio history, began on WHA when a radio guest cancels and the host decides to read a library book to fill the hour. Listeners ask for more. In 1932, it's carried as a summer program. In 1939, it becomes a daily program and continues to this day. &#13;The Larry Meiller Show - a midday show full of practical tips, traces its roots back to the earliest days of noontime weather and farm-market reports. &#13;Michael Feldman's Whad'Ya Know? - one of WPR's shows that is distributed nationwide.  This shows, offering music, humor, quizzes has been running for thirty years. &#13;To the Best of Our Knowledge - another long-running WPR show that is distributed to many other public radio stations. &#13;You can see a full list of our programs under the &quot;Shows&quot; tab on any of our webpages. You'd be hard-pressed to find another public radio organization producing as many shows.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WPRnewColorLogos.tiff</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Need to edit logo</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WCNY</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">1822</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WCNY</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">New York</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Liverpool</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.wcny.org/</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WCNY, founded in 1965 as The Educational Television Council of Central New York, is today a community-owned public media company that produces content across multiple platforms, including television and radio programs, dynamic web and targeted e-mail content, the bimonthly WCNY Connect magazine, and of course, social media. Through our use of streaming technology, we now have a global broadcast audience of viewers and listeners throughout the United States and 17 countries.&#13;As a Central New York’s public media voice and a dual licensee public broadcaster (now five television and three radio channels), serves 1.8 million households over an area that comprises about one-third of New York.  This audience relies on WCNY for local television and radio production, educational outreach, and educational web content and services.  We are an innovator in local and national programming, as evidenced by numerous awards including Emmys, for our local television programming including Cycle of Health, Financial Fitness, Insight, Double Down and Ivory Tower along with long-form documentaries.  We are the smallest city in America to have a hosted classical radio show, nearly 2000 visually-impaired community members enjoy the services of our 24/7 Readout Radio service, and the community is invited to attend our Live at Noon performances (broadcast on radio live) that feature outstanding local, regional, and national musicians and vocalists.  &#13;In our new 10,000-square-foot Education Center, we offer a wide range of educational programs for learners of all ages.  Education is central to WCNY’s mission.  Our Enterprise America program combines classroom lessons with the opportunity for students to run a model city of 14 businesses and a City Hall. Our Media Marketing Communications Career and Technical Education (CTE) course for high school students embeds students with our WCNY professionals to provide hands-on learning while also offering academic college courses.  Through experiential learning opportunities like these we aim to foster tomorrow’s entrepreneurial leaders.&#13;As the public voice for Central New York, the mission at WCNY is ‘connecting’ with and giving back to the community that supports us.  Educating, entertaining, and inspiring the public, as well as encouraging a deep appreciation for diversity and our shared humanity with content-rich programming, is what we do.  The archives provide WCNY with a way to ensure that our programming history is recorded, and that productions we have created are accessible for future generations.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">From a television perspective, Artic Air, The Barn, Central New York in the 40s, William Henry Seward: Lincoln’s Right Hand, The Performers: Taking Center Stage in NYS Agriculture, Dream Destinations: New York’s Contemporary Canals, Losing Ground: The Battle to Preserve War of 1812 Battlefields in New York State, and annual Bluegrass Ramble Picnics and Barn Dances are examples of significant local history, arts, and public affairs programming our staff has created.  The radio recordings of the now-defunct Syracuse Symphony, Live at Noon specials, and Bluegrass Ramble shows hosted by Bill Knowlton, the recipient of a Distinguished Achievement Award from the International Bluegrass Music Association for his pioneering work in the field of bluegrass music, are examples of significant radio productions created by WCNY.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WCNY_logo.jpg</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Iowa Public Television</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1770</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Iowa Public Television</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Iowa</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Johnston</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.iptv.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Community Television Foundation of South Florida, Inc</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1737</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Community Television Foundation of South Florida, Inc</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Florida</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Miami</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.wpbt2.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Vermont Public Television</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1882</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Vermont Public Television</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Vermont</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Colchester</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.vpt.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Chicago Public Radio (WBEZ-FM) and Vocalo.org</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1370</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WBEZ Chicago Public Radio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Illinois</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Chicago</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.wbez.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Rocky Mountain PBS (KRMA)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1724</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Rocky Mountain PBS</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Colorado</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Denver</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.rmpbs.org/</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KRMA-TV (Rocky Mountain PBS) first went on the air on January 30, 1956, as Denver’s instructional TV station licensed to Denver Public Schools.  As Denver’s first educational station, it broadcast for only two hours that inaugural day from a temporary studio in the Emily Griffith Opportunity School in downtown Denver.  KRMA was the 5th TV station to go on air in the Denver metro area and was Denver’s first non-commercial station.  It was the 18th educational television station in the country.&#13;Records show that as early as 1950, the Denver Public Schools, Denver Public Library, The University of Denver, the Rocky Mountain Radio Council of Denver and the Adult Education Council met to discuss educational television for Denver. In 1952, a community meeting was held to discuss the idea.  This followed the FCC’s action to set aside 242 channels in the VHG and UHF frequencies for nonprofit educational stations.  In the fall of 1953, the Denver Area Council for Educational Television was established to oversee the work and mission of KRMA for more than 30 years.&#13;On May 1, 1987, the Denver Public Schools transferred the license to the Council for Public Television, Channel 6, Inc.  Following this decision, KRMA started a capital campaign to raise $14.5 million to move on October 30, 1992 to its current studios in Denver at 1089 Bannock Street. Rocky Mountain PBS continues to be at this location today and has expanded its presence in Colorado by adding two additional studios, KTSC (Pueblo/Colorado Springs) and KRMJ (Grand Junction).&#13;In recent years, Rocky Mountain PBS has expanded by merging with [I-News][http://inewsnetwork.org/], a Colorado-based nonprofit that produces in-depth journalism for media outlets across the region and [KUVO Radio][http://kuvo.drupal.publicbroadcasting.net/], a jazz, blues and news public radio station.&#13;Rocky Mountain PBS has been on the air for 59 years and will celebrate its 60th anniversary on January 30, 2016. &#13;Each week, nearly 900,000 people throughout Colorado turn to Rocky Mountain PBS to discover inspiring local, national and international programming; find diverse viewpoints; score front row center seats to world-class performances; and experience lifelong learning opportunities. &#13;Rocky Mountain PBS is now Colorado’s only statewide television network, with stations in Denver (KRMA), Pueblo/Colorado Springs (KTSC), Steamboat Springs (KRMZ), Grand Junction (KRMJ) and Durango (KRMU).  &#13;The entire history of Rocky Mountain PBS is being archived by an award-winning volunteer-driven project known as [“Station’s Archived Memories”][http://www.rmpbs.org/volunteer/sam/] (SAM).  The archive project was founded in 2000. To date, the dedicated group of volunteers has meticulously collected and digitally archived over 50,000 photographs, 195 Oral History interviews, 15,000 Station documents, 3,500 Memorabilia pieces as well as inventoried 11,500 KRMA/Rocky Mountain PBS productions and digitally preserved 700 local programs.  To learn more about the archives at Rocky Mountain PBS or to learn how any public media station can establish an archive project, contact SAM@rmpbs.org.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Frying Pans West - (1968) Hosted by Mr. Sam Arnold and produced by Mr. Richard “Dick” Siceloff, the 1968 program is a compilation of recipes, anecdotes and little known facts about the early West and our American gastronomic heritage.&#13;Glenarm Place - (1983) Glenarm Place showcased a variety of local musical talent. It premiered May 7 1983, 10:30 PM. Produced by Kaye Lavine, hosted by Hank Troy and directed  by David Ryan.   DVD copies of “Glenarm Place” in the SAM archives.  Performances were simulcast in stereo with KCFR Radio (90.1 FM)&#13;The Naturalists - (1973) KRMA’s most ambitious projects yet was undertaken beginning March 11, 1973.  Titled “The naturalists,” it is a program about four of America’s greatest naturalists:  John Muir, Henry David Thoreau, John Burroughs and Theodore Roosevelt.  Jim Case,   KRMA’s “Special Projects Cine Unit,” under the direction of Jim Case produced the four-hour program series. Case believed the understanding of the work of these four men will be a valuable addition to the life of the nation. The four half-hour programs were produced by KRMA-TV under the supervision of the special projects director, James Case.  The objective of the series, is “to help contemporary society to re-learn the values and laws of nature these men came to slowly and naturally.” To assure accuracy, each shooting script was authenticated by a “content authority:&#45;-a man or woman who personally knew the naturalist or is an authority on his life and work.&#13;Stateline - (1983) Stateline was a program dedicated to coverage of the Colorado State legislature.&#13;Rocky Mountain Legacy - (premiered in July, 1994) Rocky Mountain Legacy sought out the stories of those who bravely faced the risks associated with any worthwhile endeavor.  Colorado was  poppulated  in the earliest days, by seekers: people seeking wealth, health or the wide open spaces of the west.  The gold rush days and the tuberculosis epidemic of the 1800s, the growth of the railroad industry in the mountain region and the Great Depression - these were just some of the reasons people were drawn to the Rocky Mountains.  Through journal entries, diaries and interviews,  the hardship and sacrifice as well as the triumph and satisfaction that built both urban and rural communities across Colorado are depicted in Rocky Mountain Legacy.  </Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">rocky_mountain_logo.jpg</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KQED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1720</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KQED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">California</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">San Francisco</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.kqed.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WJCT-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1347</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WJCT</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Florida</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Jacksonville</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.wjct.org/</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WJCT went on the air on September 10, 1958, broadcasting a report on educational television from Florida Governor Leroy Collins. Its broadcast reached Live Oak, St. Augustine, Palatka, and Folkston, Georgia. WJCT became Florida’s second educational television station, following Miami, and preceding Gainesville’s WUFT and Tampa’s WEDU by several weeks. WJCT filled its first month with “national educational television” programs from PBS’ predecessor, NET.&#13;On April 10, 1972, WJCT added its second media platform, meeting the community’s needs for fine arts and music. WJCT-FM went on the air as “Stereo 90,” broadcasting music, news and public affairs programming approximately 18 hours a day. Eighteen months later, in October 1973, Channel 7 and Stereo 90 presented their first simulcast, broadcasting a concert by the Jacksonville Symphony Orchestra.&#13;In May of 2014, the launch of the Digital Convergence Alliance Network Operations Center (DCA-NOC) marked the culmination of work begun four years prior by WJCT Public Broadcasting. WJCT spearheaded a major initiative, laying the foundation for a collaborative venture of 11 public television stations that would not only foster economies of scale but create opportunities to better serve their respective communities, the first of which is the DCA-NOC. A grant from the Corporation for Public Broadcasting (CPB) enabled WJCT and community partners to develop a technical plan for the creation of a centralized master control operation.&#13;Throughout its 56-year history, the First Coast community has been a vital component of WJCT’s success, providing individual and corporate support, contributing countless hours of volunteer work, serving on boards, partnering in productions, events and services. With continuing community support, WJCT stands poised to serve the First Coast community for another 50 years, and more, using its unique assets as a resource for citizens to come together to celebrate human diversity, experience lifelong learning, and actively engage in matters of civic importance, all to improve the quality of our lives and our community.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">First Coast Connect - Hosted by Melissa Ross, this one-hour call-in program features local newsmakers, civic and community leaders, arts, activities and more, along with spot news features and a weekly roundtable of local journalists. Launched in August 2009, First Coast Connect recently celebrated its 5th anniversary. &#13;First Coast Forum - A quarterly series of interactive community forums designed to address critical challenges facing Florida’s First Coast and to engage the community in resolving them. Each program brings First Coast business and community leaders together for discussion, and gives community members an opportunity to weigh in. Launched in July 2001, the quarterly forums broadcast live on TV and radio. &#13;Hometown - Discover the stories of the people, places and events that are unique to the Northeast Florida and Southeast Georgia area.  Hometown, produced locally by WJCT Public Broadcasting, is [available OnDemand][http://www.wjct.tv/programs/].</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WJCT_logo.jpg</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUCB (Unalaska Community Broadcasting/KIAL)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1275</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUCB Unalaska Community Broadcasting</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Alaska</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Unalaska</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://kucb.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Mississippi Public Broadcasting</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1798</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Mississippi Public Broadcasting</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Mississippi</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Jackson</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.mpbonline.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WSIU Public Broadcasting</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1752</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WSIU Public Broadcasting</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Illinois</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Carbondale</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.wsiu.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WFIU-FM (Public Radio from Indiana University)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1383</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WFIU Public Radio from Indiana University</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Indiana</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Bloomington</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://indianapublicmedia.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Thirteen - New York Public Media (WNET)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1817</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Thirteen - New York Public Media (WNET)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">New York</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">New York</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.wnet.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Twin Cities Public Television (KTCA-TV)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1797</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Twin Cities Public Television</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Minnesota</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">St. Paul</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.tpt.org/</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TPT has been around since Sept. 1957 and started as Minneapolis Educational Television. America’s 26th public TV station (KTCA). Originally housed at the University of MN. Currently, one of the top 5 public television stations in the country.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Hoop Dreams&#13;Newton’s Apple&#13;SciGirls&#13;Constitution USA with Peter Sagal</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">TPT_logo.jpg</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WVIZ/ideastream</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1831</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WVIZ/ideastream</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Ohio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Cleveland</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.ideastream.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WOSU Public Media</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1832</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WOSU Public Media</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Ohio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Columbus</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://wosu.org/</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Licensed to The Ohio State University, WOSU Public Media has been a vital community resource since 1920, when it received one of the first experimental radio licenses in the country. It has evolved into multiple public media services consisting of Classical 101 (FM); 89.7 NPR News (FM); four regional FM stations; and WOSU TV (PBS) and its sister station, WPBO TV. WOSU television covers a quarter of central and southern Ohio reaching over 900,000 households.&#13;Current major projects are led by the Columbus Neighborhoods project, developed in 2010 to focus on the history, culture and future of the community’s distinctive neighborhoods.  The Emmy and NETA Award winning initiative includes a series of major documentaries (12 over a five year period), radio programming, public engagement events including local storytelling and premieres.&#13;Other television initiatives include the arts and culture weekly series Broad &amp; High developed in 2013 as part of a local/national collaboration; the weekly public affairs program Columbus On The Record; the daily broadcast on the WOSU Ohio Channel of our local NPR radio program All Sides with Ann Fisher; and a series of national documentaries focused on explorers with ties to Ohio.  These have included John Glenn: A Life of Service and the upcoming documentary on Admiral Richard Byrd’s exploits.&#13;In 2006, WOSU opened new television studios at the COSI Science Center in downtown Columbus. All local program production is developed at the WOSU@COSI Studios, which also serves as our prime community engagement space.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Broad &amp; High&#13;Columbus On The Record&#13;All Sides with Ann Fisher</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WOSU_logo.jpg</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WNED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1815</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WNED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">New York</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Buffalo</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.wned.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1881</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Utah</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Salt Lake City</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.kued.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WBRA-TV</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1888</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Blue Ridge PBS</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Virginia</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Roanoke</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.blueridgepbs.org/</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">In 1965, a group of concerned citizens and educators established the Blue Ridge Educational Television (ETV) Association, with the goal of bringing educational television to Southwest Virginia. With seed money from the City of Roanoke and funding from nineteen area school systems, ETV then applied for state and federal grants to build the facilities. Groundbreaking for the studio building took place November 1966.&#13;On August 1, 1967, Southwest Virginia’s own public television station went on the air for the very first time as Blue Ridge Educational Television, WBRA-TV, channel 15—broadcasting from its new production facility in Roanoke. It was the nation's first all-color educational television station. WBRA’s all-color capabilities brought national attention in 1968 when RCA’s “Broadcast News Magazine” did an extensive layout about the station. Initially there were no broadcasts on weekends, and the station signed off every weekday at 11 p.m. Within those broadcast hours, WBRA staff were offering an alternative to commercial television.   In addition to broadcasts for schools, WBRA began the tradition of providing quality entertainment programming.&#13;Color programming was especially popular with educators who were using WBRA broadcasts in classrooms. During the school year, the station aired nearly seven hours of instructional programming every weekday. At that time, the station employed six studio teachers who led the daily televised lessons, which covered subjects such as science, music, geography, and economics. In 1969, instruction and entertainment were expertly combined when “Sesame Street” and “Mister Rogers’ Neighborhood” were added to WBRA’s schedule. &#13;For the first few years, WBRA’s reach was limited to portions of 15 counties surrounding the City of Roanoke. With the addition of two more transmitters, Blue Ridge PBS expanded its coverage area to the farthest corners of Southwest Virginia and into bordering counties in Kentucky, Tennessee, West Virginia, and North Carolina—a total of 26,000 square-miles. WSBN in Norton went on the air in 1971, and WMSY in Marion completed the trio of Blue Ridge PBS’ stations when it went on the air in 1981.&#13;Today people travel the world with Blue Ridge PBS, visiting distant destinations as well as special places and people across the Blue Ridge region. Blue Ridge PBS, still community owned, has grown into a 21st century, multimedia organization. It is now the region’s story teller, serving 2.5 million individuals as an around-the-clock source for thoughtful news and documentaries, arts and culture programming, and the best in children’s television.&#13;In recent years, investments in digital technologies have enabled Blue Ridge PBS to triple the amount of programming available to regional viewers. Viewers can now choose from three digital channels: Blue Ridge PBS, Southwest Virginia Public TV and World.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Blue Ridge Nightline was a public affairs show that was on the air for over 20 years covering a wide variety of topics.  The show had a number of title variations over the years as hosts changed.  Several episodes of Hake Wheeler’s Nightline were part of the collection we digitized for the archives project.   &#13;Blue Ridge PBS worked with nationally known historian, James I. Robertson, Jr. to produce a 10 part series on the Civil War.&#13;In addition, the station produced a 3 hour documentary on Virginia in the Civil War to commemorate the 150th anniversary of the war.  This program was broken down into modules and designed specifically for use in the schools.  A set of the DVDs went to each school in Virginia.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WBRA_logo.jpg</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KVIE</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1716</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KVIE</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">California</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Sacramento</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.kvie.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KRCB</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1709</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KRCB</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">California</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Rohnert Park</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.krcb.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WYSU 88.5 FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1571</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WYSU</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Ohio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Youngstown</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://wysu.org/</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">In 1969, just two years after the proposal was first made for a fine arts radio station in Youngstown, Ohio, with the hard work of Don Elser, first director Steve Grcevich, and Youngstown State University president Albert Pugsley, WYSU-FM signed on the air at 88.5 MHZ, licensed to Youngstown State University.  The date was October 23, and the time was 10:00 am, with program host Bill Foster introducing Richard Strauss’ Also sprach Zarathustra.  The station began by broadcasting 12 hours daily from its studios in the former Valley Park Motel on Wick Avenue, and served Youngstown State University and the Mahoning Valley community.  WYSU-FM is a charter member of National Public Radio. Some of the first programs to air were NPR’s All Things Considered, WYSU’s Folk Festival with Charles Darling, and the syndicated program Adventures in Good Music with Karl Haas.  &#13;With a small staff, WYSU made great strides over the next decades, becoming part of the first radio network using satellite-delivered programs in 1971, moving to new studios in 1976, and expanding to a 24-hour broadcast day in 1980.  Also in 1980, WYSU held its first on-air pledge drive, a practice that continues twice yearly, and remains a major source of funding for the station.  &#13;Under the guidance of director Robert Peterson in the 1980s and 1990s, the station began airing Morning Edition and operating a new 50,000 watt transmitter.  The addition of translators in nearby Ashtabula, Ohio and New Wilmington, Pennsylvania expanded WYSU’s coverage.  In 1996, state of the art digital editing equipment was installed, and overnight programs became automated.&#13;In the late 1990s, WYSU collaborated with the McDonough Museum of Contemporary Art at YSU in launching the first Mad About the Arts event – a celebration of great art, food, music and dance.  The event is now in its 20th successful year of raising funds to support both organizations.  In 2000, classical music host Barbara Krauss planned the first station-sponsored European tour to Great Britain.  The tours have since taken groups of WYSU travelers all over the world. &#13;Gary Sexton, WYSU’s current director of broadcasting, took the position in 2000.  Under his direction, a WYSU website (wysu.org) was established, as well as streaming audio. By 2004, digital equipment was installed in the broadcast studios.  WYSU began broadcasting in HD in 2007, adding an all classical HD channel a year later.  In tandem with these advances, the station continues to produce music and community affairs programs with local hosts and guests.  Fund drives have continued to be successful and the staff and supporting members remain committed to WYSU’s mission as a public radio station:  to be the community’s leading source for trusted, in-depth news, engaging conversation, and music that stimulates the mind and spirit.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Looking Out - This round-table discussion is a platform for community leaders address national and global issues from often unexplored angles. Hosted by Dr. George McCloud the half-hour program covers many topics ranging from the economy to foreign policy, and ecology to education.&#13;Lincoln Avenue - Hosted by Dr. Sherry Linkon, Lincoln Avenue focused on new ideas and developments in the local community, on campus, and across the world. The program invited community and academic leaders, innovators, and critics to explain their work and why it matters.  It aired on WYSU for almost 10 years, ending in 2012.&#13;Doing Good - Designed to raise social consciousness and public awareness about salient concerns in our community, Doing Good also highlights good work and honest efforts being directed at issues important to the Mahoning Valley.  This one-on-one interview program is hosted by Gina Marinelli,  a former local news anchor and journalist, and encourages listeners to become engaged and involved in projects and activities featured on the show.&#13;Locally hosted music programs have been part of WYSU programming since 1969.  They include classical, jazz and folk music</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WYSU_logo.jpg</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Prairie Public Broadcasting</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1826</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Prairie Public Broadcasting</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">North Dakota</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Fargo</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.prairiepublic.org/</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">What began with a hand-me-down trailer house headquarters and television transmitter tower on the edge of Fargo, North Dakota, is now a television and radio network that serves North Dakota, portions of its border states, and several communities in Manitoba, Canada. In service to households in the region for 50 years, Prairie Public is not showing signs of being over-the-hill. Rather, it continues to embrace technological advances in the medium while remaining remarkably close to the same mission it has had from the beginning—to deliver programs that educate, involve, and inspire, without commercial interruption. &#13;The organization was conceived in August of 1959 when a forward-thinking Dr. Ted Donat presided over the incorporation of the North Central Educational Television Association. In July of 1963, after nearly four years of planning and development, the first employee was hired, and North Central Educational Television was about to go live. The Association’s first station, KFME-TV (Channel 13, Fargo), aired its first broadcast in January of 1964.&#13;That first public television signal was an abbreviated three-hour schedule. Prairie Public’s first local production, an English Literature course for Moorhead Minnesota’s Concordia College, began in 1965. KFME began broadcasting in color in 1967, the same year President Johnson signed The Public Broadcasting Act. &#13;North Central Educational Television had a growth spurt in the ‘70s, changed its name to Prairie Public Television, and expanded its broadcast area to include the entire state of North Dakota. In the ‘80s, radio broadcasts were added, and the brand has since changed to Prairie Public.&#13;Prairie Public is proud of its award-winning television documentaries, including an award-winning series about the history and culture of the Germans from Russia, a series of documentaries in collaboration with the Plains CO2 Reduction Partnership led by the University of North Dakota’s Energy &amp; Environmental Research Center, the nationally broadcast “Painting with Paulson” art instruction series, and documentaries about Homesteading, Prairie Churches, the Old Red Trail, Scandinavian Traditions, regional artists and musicians, and many more.&#13;Prairie Public has embraced new technology, adding web content, social media communications and online viewing and listening. The switch from analogue to digital broadcasting—Prairie Public was the first in the region to do so—allowed for more great programming for schools, more hours of non-violent children’s programming for families, and the stunning clarity of high-definition television. Just as the public adjusted from black and white color back in the ‘60’s, large high-definition televisions have become the norm in most households as Prairie Public turns 50.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:Index="9"><Data ss:Type="String">Prairie_logo.jpg</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Cincinnati Public Radio (WGUC-FM, WMUB-FM, WVXU-FM)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1559</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Cincinnati Public Radio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Ohio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Cincinnati</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.cincinnatipublicradio.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUSC-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1297</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUSC-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">California</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Los Angeles</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.kusc.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Nine Network of Public Media (formerly KETC)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1800</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Nine Network of Public Media</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Missouri</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">St. Louis</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://ninenet.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Arkansas Educational TV Network (AETN)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1708</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Arkansas Educational TV Network</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Arkansas</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Conway</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.aetn.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Mountain Lake PBS (WCFE)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1818 </Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Mountain Lake PBS</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">New York</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Plattsburgh</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://mountainlake.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WGBY</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1784</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WGBY</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Massachusetts</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Springfield</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://wgby.org/</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WGBY-TV (formerly known as Channel 57) a division of WGBH Educational Foundation began its broadcasting service in Springfield, Massachusetts as the western link of the Massachusetts Public Broadcasting Network on September 26, 1971.&#13;WGBY has a demographic of over 950,000.  It is extremely proud of its award winning documentaries and story- telling skills that celebrate local heritage and individuals, its weekly WGBY produced local programming, its education and outreach programs that compliment and expand its programming through a multiple of media venues, and its numerous partnerships with organization throughout its entire viewing area.  These programs are all imprinted with WGBY’s mission to connect the people of our region with ideas, events and each other.  WGBY is unique in public broadcasting.  While licensed to the WGBH Educational Foundation by the FCC and operates under the Foundation’s IRS status, WGBY has been programmed and managed separately since 1971.  WGBY holds its own membership in the Public Broadcasting Service.  &#13;Today, WGBY-TV continues to engage, educate, explore, and entertain.   As in 1971, WGBY strives to be a unique community asset worthy of being considered by the citizens as the foremost public television station for western New England.&#13;</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Connecting Point - WGBY continues to present a 3-night- a-week look at news headlines and feature content.  Each magazine style program features interviews, analysis, field production, and commentary focused on the communities in western New England that we serve.  &#13;Together in Song - WGBY continues to celebrate the living choral tradition in western New England with our original series Together In Song.  Judges and viewers select the top 7 ensembles out of 40 who participate each year. Those 7 groups perform live on stage with a studio audience plus viewers at home who tuned in for the event. This audience interactive series, hosted by Kevin Rhodes, Music Director of the Springfield Symphony Orchestra, showcases the talents of over a thousand singers from throughout the WGBY viewing area each season. &#13;As Schools Match Wits - As Schools Match Wits is a treasured western New England institution.  This series is a co-production and partnering with Westfield State University .   As Schools Match Wits is an academic quiz show competition open to both public and private high schools throughout western New England (including MA, CT &amp; VT), and is one of the longest-running shows of its kind in the nation.  ASMW showcases the best and brightest high school students that western NE has to offer, allowing them to shine in a venue which celebrates learning.&#13;Latino Youth Media Institute (LYMI) - WGBY’s vision for the Latino Youth Media Institute is to give young Latinos who have an interest in pursuing a career in media an opportunity to explore their choice of media through an internship, with the hope that they will continue their education in that field.  The institute’s purpose is to assist more Latinos in entering communications fields as journalists, television or radio producers, hosts, writers, etc. &#13;Telling Our Legacies Digitally (TOLD) - WGBY’s TOLD is a community-based digital storytelling project that is designed to engage members of our communities.  In this series of interactive workshops, participants learn through a fun, hands-on, team-building approach and are guided through a process that combines storytelling with modern-day technology. Participants write their own scripts, create storyboards, and record their voices. Each participant also learns how to edit photographs, add effects, and use video software to assemble all of these elements into a “digital story.” At the end of the workshop, WGBY invites peers, family, and community to a public screening of the stories where participants talk about their experience in the workshop. The screenings are remarkable, healing, and transformational. The stories give voice to the voiceless, strengthen literacy, stimulate dialogue, and build community. These digital stories preserve the history, culture, ideas, and legacies of our community.&#13;</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WGBY_logo.jpg</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KDLG-AM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1259</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KDLG</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Alaska</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Dillingham</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://kdlg.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WQED-TV</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1846</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WQED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Pennsylvania</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Pittsburgh</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.wqed.org/</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WQED was the nation’s first community-supported television station and went on the air on April 1, 1954.  In 1973, Classical WQED-FM 89.3 was founded as the region’s only 24-hour classical radio station.&#13;Today, WQED is educational public media with four television programming streams: WQED-TV; WQED: The Neighborhood Channel; WQED: The Create Channel; and WQED Showcase; three radio streams: WQED-FM 89.3; WQEJ-FM 89.7/Johnstown; The Pittsburgh Concert Channel at WQED-FM HD-2 and www.wqed.org/fm online provide WQED content to all residents in the viewing and listening area, and online around the world;  local and national television and radio productions; WQED Interactive, and iQ: smartmedia, WQED’s Educational initiative. &#13;Throughout its history, WQED has partnered with hundreds of local community organizations toward improvements in education; arts and culture; community health; economics; and important local issues through its form of civic journalism.  As the only community-owned multimedia resource in the region, WQED is a convener, a central gathering place, and a conduit for other local non-profit organizations. &#13;WQED has exported the region nationally with projects like The War That Made America, a four part historical documentary on the French and Indian War that aired nationwide on PBS; national cooking shows with Chris Fennimore; the Doo Wop music franchise; weekly national radio broadcasts of the Pittsburgh Symphony Orchestra and a continuing series of local and national documentaries by Emmy Award-winning producer Rick Sebak. &#13;WQED’s latest national production, August Wilson: The Ground On Which I Stand, is slated to air nationally on PBS American Masters in February 2015.  The documentary will focus on the life and work of Pittsburgh-native and Pulitzer Prize-winning playwright August Wilson and will include and extensive educational initiative in key cities across the country. &#13;WQED is one of the busiest producers of local programming in the PBS system.  In addition to the local and national documentaries, WQED produces and airs local programs that capture the stories of advancement, arts and diversity in our region. &#13;Classical WQED-FM is “the voice of the arts in western Pennsylvania” by highlighting all that the station has meant for the region with retrospectives, tributes, community events, and celebrations. WQED-FM has offered classical and fine arts and cultural programs since its inception in 1973, allowing listeners to hear live and recorded classical performances and learn the latest arts and culture news from Pittsburgh and around the world. Listeners can hear WQED-FM at 89.3 and on its repeater stations, WQED-FM89.7 /Johnstown. &#13;WQED Interactive, a media portal to the world, makes the aforementioned WQED programs all the more accessible to viewers and listeners, any time, and any place. WQED reaches more than 37,000 people through social media. &#13;iQ: smartmedia is our strategy for education to capitalize on what kids have inside of them and to capture that potential. Around it revolves all of WQED's educational goals and objectives: to provide new tools and models, thought leadership, research, and training on the intersection of media and learning to prepare our children for a competitive world. We provide content for science and technology; literacy; global cultures and connections; expression; social and community responsibility; numeracy; and behavioral wellness.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:Index="9"><Data ss:Type="String">WQED_logo.jpg</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KYUK</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1703</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KYUK</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Alaska</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Bethel</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://kyuk.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">UNC-TV</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1824</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">UNC-TV</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">North Carolina</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Research Triangle Park</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.unctv.org/</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Today, UNC-TV is the 12-station statewide public television network for North Carolina, reaching all 100 counties with four channels of national and local program content, as well as parts of Virginia, South Carolina, Tennessee and Georgia.  A lot has changed since WUNC-TV in Chapel Hill signed on as the nation’s tenth “educational television” station on January 8, 1955, largely due to the efforts of three visionary leaders.  William C. “Billy” Carmichael, the University of North Carolina’s vice president for finance, University alumnus and famous band lead Kay Kyser, and eventual university president William Friday – then the assistant to the university’s president, Gordon Gray – spearheaded an effort to use the burgeoning power of television to bring non-commercial educational content to the citizens of the state.  This group recognized the unique opportunity when the Federal Communications Commission offered eight channels in North Carolina for non-commercial uses in 1952.  They traveled the state marshaling contributions and support for both public and private funding, and so UNC-TV was born.&#13;William Friday became president of the university system in 1957, and during his legendary 30 year tenure in that position, he continued to be a powerful and effective advocate for the importance and value of public television.  Gradually, it transitioned from an operation run primarily by students and faculty members to a fully professional broadcasting organization.  With the advent of PBS in 1968, UNC-TV was transformed from the old educational television model to being a source for mission-driven programming for general audiences.  In the meantime, UNC-TV continued to expand its reach, gradually adding transmitter sites to cover more of the state.  In 1979, the University of North Carolina Center for Public Television was established by the university’s board of governors, and 10 years later operations were finally consolidated in one location, the network’s current headquarters and studios in Research Triangle Park.&#13;In many ways, the much-beloved William Friday was the face of UNC-TV.  In addition to his advocacy and leadership as university president, he was also the host of the longest-running program in UNC-TV history, North Carolina People with William Friday.  The program went on the air in 1971 and continued its weekly run until President Friday passed away at the age of 92 in October, 2012.  In a warm and informal one-on-one interview format, Friday engaged North Carolinians from all walks of life, from the exalted to the humble, coaxing out the stories that make every life interesting, and his viewing audience remained loyal throughout his life. In 2014 the Board of Governors of the National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences, Nashville/Midsouth Chapter, honored William Friday with posthumous induction as the inaugural member of its Gold Circle for his exceptional service to the advancement of public television.  At the same time, the chapter also presented UNC-TV with its Governor’s Award in recognition of the network’s history of exemplary service to the state of North Carolina.&#13;Today, UNC-TV not only brings programming from PBS, the BBC and other sources to the entire state, it produces more than 300 hours of original programming each year for and about North Carolina.  Looking to the future, UNC-TV continues extending its content into the ever-growing array of digital platforms, and expanding its mission to include even more opportunities for public service.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">North Carolina People with William Friday</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">UNCTV_logo.jpg</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:Height="90">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WMHT</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1820</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WMHT</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">New York</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Troy</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.wmht.org/</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">A trusted community resource for over half a century, WMHT Educational Telecommunications uses the power of non-commercial public television, radio, the web and other media to enrich the lives of more than a half million households throughout eastern New York state and portions of western Vermont, Massachusetts and Connecticut. Television broadcast channels include WMHT-DT, WMHT-Create  and WMHT-WORLD.  Radio stations operated by WMHT include WMHT-FM 89.1 &amp; WRHV-FM 88.7 (classical public radio) and WEXT 97.7 (AAA public radio).  WMHT also operates RISE, a radio reading service for the visually and print disabled. In addition, WMHT offers numerous community outreach and family learning initiatives that inspire, educate and entertain for a lifetime.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s257"><Data ss:Type="String">New York Now&#13;William Kennedy’s Prohibition Story&#13;Rediscovering the Light&#13;The Track at Saratoga: America’s Grandest Race Course&#13;Divine Discontent&#13;Nine Long Days</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WMHT_logo.jpg</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WRNI (Rhode Island Public Radio)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">4844</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Rhode Island Public Radio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Rhode Island</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Providence</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://ripr.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Appalshop, Inc. (WMMT and Appalshop Films)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1419</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Appalshop, Inc.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Kentucky</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Whitesburg</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.appalshop.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KMOS</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1802</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KMOS</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Missouri</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Warrensburg</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://kmos.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Film &amp; Media Archive, Washington University in St. Louis</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NCSG16</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Film and Media Archive, Washington University in St. Louis</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Missouri</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">St. Louis</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.library.wustl.edu/units/spec/filmandmedia/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Oregon Public Broadcasting (OPB)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1840</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Oregon Public Broadcasting</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Orgeon</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Portland</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.opb.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WXPN-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1595</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WXPN</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Pennsylvania</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Philadelphia</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.xpn.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WTIU (Public Television from Indiana University)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1761</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WTIU Public Television from Indiana University</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Indiana</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Bloomington</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://indianapublicmedia.org/tv/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WGVU Public TV &amp; Radio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1789</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WGVU Public TV and Radio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Michigan</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Grand Rapids</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.wgvu.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Iowa Public Radio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1393</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Iowa Public Radio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Iowa</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Des Moines</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://iowapublicradio.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">New Hampshire Public Radio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1502</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">New Hampshire Public Radio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">New Hampshire</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Concord</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://nhpr.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WXXI Public Broadcasting (WXXI-TV)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1531</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WXXI Public Broadcasting</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">New York</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Rochester</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://interactive.wxxi.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KCAW-FM  (Raven Radio Foundation, Inc.)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1271</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Raven Radio Foundation, Inc.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Alaska</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Sitka</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.kcaw.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KNME</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1810</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">New Mexico PBS</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">New Mexico</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Albuquerque</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.newmexicopbs.org/</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KNME-TV signed on the air in 1958 as the first public “educational” television station in New Mexico.  Licensed to both the University of New Mexico and Albuquerque Public Schools, KNME-TV is unique in broadcasting with this diverse, collaborative licensee structure. New Mexico PBS serves the people of New Mexico by providing engaging local and national content, in-depth news and public affairs, digital media, education and outreach services, lifelong learning, an interactive web site, and a celebration of arts and culture.&#13;As the television industry has matured and changed so has KNME-TV.  Our history of accomplishments includes a number of groundbreaking television shows like Dr. George Fishbeck’s Science, Colores!, and New Mexico in Focus.  KNME was the first television station in New Mexico to broadcast a digital signal and to adopt the new digital high-definition standard on a continuous basis.   KNME-TV is one of the most watched public television stations in the country reaching almost 700,000 households each week with 20,000 members in central and northern New Mexico.&#13;In 2009, KNMD-TV joined KNME-TV as a second Public Television service, providing enlightening and entertaining programming in support of New Mexico’s education systems.  This increase in capacity, concurrent with innovations in on-line delivery of content, and expansion of our satellite distribution services drove the need for a new umbrella brand, New Mexico PBS.  &#13;New Mexico PBS operates two digital high power transmitters and 33 low-power translators to provide free over the air viewing to the people of New Mexico.  These transmitters provided greater than 99% reliability during the past year.  New Mexico PBS recently added a new translator to the Shiprock area which serves the Navajo Nation.&#13;New Mexico PBS has extensive partnerships throughout the community.  These partnerships include the K-12 community, higher-education, dozens of community service organizations and more.  Our broad reach on-air, on-line and on the ground comprise an extensive educational and community service organization in New Mexico.  New Mexico PBS’ Ready to Learn Service impacts the lives of thousands of children in New Mexico presenting over 90 workshops for parents and caregivers and distributing thousands of books.&#13;New Mexico PBS provides important local programming to the citizens of New Mexico. New Mexico PBS productions have won national and regional awards including a Peabody Award, a national Emmy, and 40 regional Emmys.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Colores! - Our weekly cultural affairs series looks at the inspiration, challenges, and processes of a wide range of local and national artists, authors, actors, musicians and more.  COLORES! is presented though a collaboration between new Mexico PBS and the Public Television Major Market Group (MMG), a public television affinity group.   Colores! is funded by The Frederick Hammersley Foundation.&#13;Public Square - brings together community leaders and citizens for an impassioned and informed discussion about some of the biggest issues facing our children today.  Topics included youth mental health, women’s economic empowerment in New Mexico, transitioning out of foster care, early brain development, impact of domestic violence on children and access to children’s healthcare. Public Square is funded by a grant from the W.K. Kellogg Foundation.&#13;New Mexico In Focus - is New Mexico PBS’ prime-time weekly news magazine show covering the events, issues, and people that are shaping life in New Mexico and the Southwest. Hosted by Gene Grant, New Mexico In Focus provides in-depth coverage of issues and on topics including politics, health care, drought, economic development and more.&#13;New Mexico PBS produces inspiring and informative programs showcasing the beauty, culture and history of the American Southwest with programs such as Balloon Fiesta, Painting Taos, The Sandias.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">newmexicoPBS_logo.jpg</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KXCI Community Radio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1283</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KXCI Community Radio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Arizona</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Tucson</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">https://kxci.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Friends of WWOZ, Inc.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1427</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WWOZ</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Louisiana</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">New Orleans</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.wwoz.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Ozarks Public Broadcasting (KOZK/KOZJ)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1801</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Ozarks Public Television</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Missouri</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Springfield</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.optv.org/</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Ozarks Public Television is the Missouri State licensee for KOZK-TV, channel 21 in Springfield, Missouri and KOZJ-TV, channel 26 in Joplin, Missouri.&#13;As a university licensee, KOZK's studios and offices are located on the Missouri State University campus in Springfield.&#13;Ozarks Public Television provides PBS programming and instructional television services to 549,540 households in Southwest Missouri and the adjoining three state area. OPTV broadcasts 168 hours of programming per week with a supporting membership of about 6,500 members and over 100 corporate and institutional underwriters.&#13;Strong local community commitment, support, and involvement provides a volunteer staff augmenting station operations in a variety of tasks. Volunteers provide support in production, administrative, and fundraising tasks, including operation of two televised auctions.&#13;KOZJ/channel 26, a &quot;satellite&quot; station of KOZK/Springfield, began broadcasting in 1986. Although a Missouri State licensee, the business office is located in downtown Joplin with transmission facilities located at KODE, the Joplin ABC affiliate.&#13;Ozarks Public Television offices and studios are located in Strong Hall on the Missouri State University campus in Springfield, Missouri.&#13;We strive to ensure we capture the history and heritage that has made the Ozarks a great place to live.  Just like everyone else we are a small staff trying to do a lot of work that informs, educates and entertains our viewers.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">OzarksWatch Video Magazine – The goal of the series is to increase a knowledge and understanding of the region.  The series began in 1999, and we do approximately 12 to 15 new shows a year.  It airs weekly and documents, presents and preserves the unique heritage of the Ozarks.  We have over 210 episodes completed over the years and they can be seen by going to our website.&#13;Local Documentaries – We produced our first local documentary in 2003 entitled, Ozark Jubilee:  A Living Legacy.  After that we started doing one new one a year and now we are producing two local documentaries each year.  They have a wide range of topics and have been a huge success for our station.  Again, a list of these productions are on our website as well.  The last two we did this year was Stately Images: The Public Art of Missouri’s State Capitol (it was a 30 minute program based on all the art work that is in our state capitol building in Jefferson City, including many painting by Thomas Hart Benton) and the second program was Links to the Past, Fairways to the Future (it was a 90 minute documentary that centered around the history of golf in the Ozarks which dates back over 100 years and went all the  present).  We are currently sitting on 17 documentaries (ranging from 30 to 120 minutes in length with two more for 2015 in production now).&#13;Passport to China – This is a series of 12 programs that we produced to help people become better acquainted with the people, customs, traditions and language of China.  MSU currently has over 800 students enrolled from China and in return we send students and faculty members to China.  The programs provide insight to the culture of Chinese people, take people in the Ozarks to places they may have only read about and show them how much we are alike.  It has been a very successful series and we are currently preparing to do a new series of shows about South America, Central America, Mexico and Cuba.  That series will begin in January of 2016.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Ozarks_logo.jpg</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KDNA-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1653</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KDNA</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Washington</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Granger</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.kdna.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WFYI-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1388</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WFYI</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Indiana</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Indianapolis</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.wfyi.org/</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Known for quality programming throughout Central Indiana, WFYI Public Media provides more than just the standard radio and television services. WFYI has been involved as a community leader and partner in education, health, public affairs, and the arts since 1970. We serve as a public forum where people are encouraged to discuss and debate issues important to the local community. Our award-winning documentaries and public affairs programs have addressed many relevant topics ‒ including financial literacy, healthcare, workforce development and environmental affairs. This broadcast schedule combines with local community outreach programs to focus on developing successful solutions to local issues.&#13;Forty-three years ago WFYI Public Media was formed after many local residents in Central Indiana voiced the need to create the state’s first educational television system. A local community leader, Ardath Y. Burkhart, passionately led a small grass-roots campaign to create a local educational television station. This group became affectionately known as &quot;Ardath's Army&quot; and quickly gained community support by traveling door-to-door across Indianapolis and its six surrounding counties. The volunteers pushed the station into existence in just a few short weeks by raising enough money to cover a full year of operating expenses. The station first signed on the air with a no-frills staff of nine employees, three black-and-white television cameras, and a signal that reached just beyond downtown Indianapolis. WFYI was the city's first UHF television signal and the only channel to provide commercial-free programming ‒ a novel idea, even 40 years ago.&#13;Now, more than 80 professionals work hard at WFYI Public Media to make it Indiana’s chief PBS and NPR member station and one of Central Indiana’s leading not-for-profits. The WFYI headquarters is a state-of-the-art facility conveniently situated at 1630 N. Meridian St. in Indianapolis. The WFYI location is one of Indianapolis' premier media hubs and centers for civic engagement.&#13;As WFYI Public Media looks towards the future, it will continue to focus on expanding its local production capacity; enhancing its community services to both mainstream and underserved audiences; and building on its proven track record of delivering first-rate local, national and international news coverage.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Across Indiana – for 20 seasons, WFYI correspondents traveled the state to explore the passions, eccentricities and history of the residents of the Hoosier state. &#13;The Natural Heritage of Indiana – Three part documentary series shot over a two-year period revealing Indiana’s natural wonders in spectacular detail. &#13;Fleeced: Speaking Out Against Senior Financial Abuse – A documentary revealing the extent of fraud. &#13;Indiana Expeditions - One of the state’s most honored and respected teachers on a journey to discover how real science impacts our lives every day. &#13;CBC - Communities Building Community with former Indiana First Lady Judy O’Bannon showcased the extraordinary ways in which Indiana residents are working together to improve the quality of life in their communities.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WFYI-logo.jpg</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WDVX-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">4721</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WDVX-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Tennessee</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Knoxville</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.wdvx.com/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WUFT-TV</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1735</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WUFT-TV</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Florida</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Gainesville</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.wuft.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KWSO-FM (Warm Springs Community Radio)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">4502</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KWSO</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Oregon</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Warm Springs</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://kwso.org/</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Confederated Tribes of Warm Springs (CTWS) is a federally recognized Indian Tribe located in Central Oregon 104 miles south of Portland and 60 miles north of Bend, just off Highway 26. The Warm Springs Reservation consists of 640,000 acres and is home to three (3) tribes, the Warm Springs, Wasco, and Paiute Tribes.&#160; KWSO 91.9 FM is a Non-Commercial Community radio station owned and operated by the Tribes and first aired in September 1986. With 4,300 watts of power, and a transmitter atop Eagle Butte, KWSO broadcasts 7 days a week, 24 hours a day. The radio station broadcasts local news and information, cultural programming and music and reaches 50,000 people in all of Jefferson County and into Wasco, Crook and Deschutes Counties with a primary focus on the residents of the Warm Springs Indian Reservation.&#160; In 2009 KWSO moved into the Warm Springs Media Center which was funded by the CTWS, Meyer Memorial Trust and the Corporation for Public Broadcasting Community Service Grant Program. This eco-friendly building features a 11.4 kilowatt solar panel array and also houses the Spilyay Tymoo, a community newspaper published by the CTWS.&#160; The mission of KWSO radio is to provide Warm Springs with quality radio programming that: delivers local news and information; promotes education, cultural knowledge and language preservation; and increases awareness of social, health and safety issues.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Warm Springs Program and Our People and Mother Earth - KWSO continues ongoing production of these weekly news magazines. &#13;Talking Drum - KWSO produced this show for the NV1 network for several years, and formerly produced “Groove Central Radio.” &#13;Veterans Day programming- KWSO alters format to honor veterans with special programming all day on Veteran’s Day, featuring history of Native American Service and interviews with local Veterans from the past and present.&#160; There is currently 12 hours of locally produced Veteran's Day content. &#13;We Shall Remain - KWSO produces this [radio hour][http://www.prx.org/series/31158-we-shall-remain]</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KWSO_logo.jpg</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WOJB-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1666</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WOJB-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Wisconsin</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Hayward</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.wojb.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KNBA-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1254</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Koahnic Broadcast Corporation</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Alaska</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Anchorage</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://knba.org/</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Koahnic Broadcast Corporation was created as a non-profit media corporation in 1992 by Alaska Native leaders to preserve culture and languages, combat widespread misconceptions and prejudices against Alaska Natives, and create cross-cultural bridges. Since our creation, Koahnic Broadcast Corporation has been a national leader in Native American radio broadcasting, media production, and training. &#13;Koahnic operates KNBA 90.3 FM in Anchorage, Alaska, the first urban Native radio station, which signed on in October 1996. KNBA broadcasts news, public affairs and contemporary music to Anchorage and surrounding areas, and streams its signal online. KNBA also produces special programming, such as annual broadcast coverage of the Alaska Federation of Natives Convention that is carried by stations across the state.&#13;Koahnic is the nation’s primary producer and distributor of Native public radio programming. Koahnic’s award-winning national radio programs include: Native America Calling, a weekday one-hour live moderated call-in program; National Native News, a weekday 5-minute news feature that has been recognized repeatedly by the Native American Journalists Association; and Earthsongs, a dynamic weekly feature spotlighting contemporary Native music. &#13;Starting in 2006, Koahnic has operated Native Voice One (NV1), the national Native radio program distribution service. Through NV1 distribution, Native radio programs reach the majority of the Alaska Native population and the American Indian reservation audience through carriage by most of the country’s 55 Native-owned stations. NV1 programs are also heard on public radio stations serving urban areas including Atlanta, Orlando, Phoenix, and Sacramento, as well as smaller cities like Duluth, Minnesota; Bloomington, Indiana; Salt Lake City, Utah; and Asheville, North Carolina. &#13;NV1 station affiliation includes 400 public radio stations and repeaters, including 50 Native stations in rural communities. Many more listeners access the NV1 and KNBA webstreams on mobile devices to hear these shows that are engaging Native America.&#13;</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">National Native News (NNN) - a daily five-minute newscast, has been the leading daily news service focused on Native issues for 27 years. NNN is the only news program of this kind produced and anchored entirely by a Native staff.  Broadcast Monday through Friday on more than 300 U.S. and Canadian radio stations and their translators, NNN is anchored and produced by Antonia Gonzales (Navajo), with reporters contributing stories from across the country.&#13;Native America Calling (NAC) - broadcast live nationwide, is an intense and stimulating one-hour call-in radio talk show. NAC is produced by Koahnic five days a week and broadcast via NV1 to stations across the country. There is no other national forum in any medium for this kind of exchange on Native issues. Native and non-Native leaders in government, business and the arts recognize this and take advantage of the opportunity to participate in NAC’s talking circle. Both members of rural and reservation Native communities and Native people listening from urban areas may call in and speak directly to people closest to Native issues. Since 1995 NAC has provided links between Native and non-Native people, enabling callers to speak out on a variety of subjects that educate and enlighten their communities and other public radio audiences. Hosted by Tara Gatewood (Isleta), the program is broadcast on nearly 100 Native and public radio stations and translators.&#13;Earthsongs - a weekly public radio program produced in Alaska and distributed nationally via NV1. Since 1999, Earthsongs has been the primary showcase for contemporary Native American and Indigenous music and culture. Hosted and produced by Alexis Sallee (Iñupiaq and Mexican-American), the hour-long program is carried by nearly 100 public radio stations across 16 states, and streamed online. Each hour of Earthsongs features exclusive artist interviews, and a carefully curated mix of music by both emerging and established Native musicians.  &#13;The Alaska Federation of Natives (AFN) Convention is the largest representative annual gathering in the United States of any Native peoples. Each year, the AFN Convention draws between 4,000–5,000 attendees. Policy guidelines and advocacy statements are set by the dozens of resolutions passed by voting delegates at the Convention. Since 1996, KNBA has produced and broadcast statewide, gavel-to-gavel coverage of this important three-day event. The broadcasts are aired on KNBA, streamed online, and made available to stations across the state. In the last decade, KNBA has added additional coverage from the event, including daily five-minute newscasts both in English and in Native languages including Iñupiaq, Athabascan, Tlingit and Yup’ik and a special hour-long discussion program, “Alaska’s Native Voice.” KNBA’s live, statewide broadcasts from the AFN Convention provide an important service to Alaskans, enabling listeners to stay in touch with important discussions and debates. &#13;2010 Inuit Nipaat Radio - Koahnic Broadcast Corporation was the invited United States media provider for the 2010 General Assembly of the Inuit Circumpolar Council (ICC) in Nuuk, Greenland. “Nipaat” is a Greenlandic and Iñupiaq word meaning “Sound,” and the broadcasts’ title was chosen to reflect the concept that this special coverage had a distinct “Inuit Sound” or “Inuit Voice” to speak to Native people throughout the circumpolar region. Koahnic provided context, detail and analysis throughout the four-day proceedings with daily broadcasts. As part of the broadcasts, Koahnic produced five-minute recaps of each day's proceedings in English, Iñupiaq, Yup'ik and Greenlandic. The program was aired not only by KNBA in Anchorage, but by rural stations serving communities throughout Alaska including in Dillingham, Nome, Bethel, Chevak, Kotzebue, Barrow and Sand Point.&#13;</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Koahnic_logo.jpg</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUNM (aka KNME-FM)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1507</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUNM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">New Mexico</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Albuquerque</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://kunm.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Vermont Public Radio - WVPR</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1642</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Vermont Public Radio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Vermont</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Colchester</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.vpr.net/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WYCC-TV20 PBS Chicago</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1755</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WYCC-TV20 PBS Chicago</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Illinois</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Chicago</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.wycc.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WHYY</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1844</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WHYY</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Pennsylvania</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Philadelphia</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.whyy.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WKAR</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1787</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WKAR</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Michigan</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">East Lansing</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://wkar.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KOCE/PBS SoCal</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1710</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PBS SoCaL</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">California</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Costa Mesa</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.pbssocal.org/</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Over four decades, PBS SoCaL has grown into a cultural resource for all of Southern California. In 2011, when Southern California abruptly lost what had been its lead PBS station, PBS SoCaL— then known as KOCE-TV for Orange County— adapted quickly to ensure that Southern California would continue to receive free community services from the nation’s most trusted media brand. PBS SoCaL continues to grow with an expanding service area that now includes LA County and the Inland Empire. PBS SoCaL is the parent to three unique broadcast channels, PBS SoCaL HD, PBS SoCaL Plus, and PBS SoCaL World, dedicated to educating, entertaining and enlightening viewers throughout the Southland.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PBS SoCaL’s production history under its former name, KOCE-TV, included content about Orange County and California.&#160; The archive collection includes the “Orange County History Project,” and a statewide documentary series called “California Dreams.”&#160; Public affairs series such as “Jim Cooper’s Orange County” included many local election debates.&#160; The assimilation of Southeast Asian immigrants following the Vietnam War was a significant content topic. The collection includes interviews with Pres. Gerald Ford, William F. Buckley, Howard Jarvis and many former Governors and US Senators.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PBS_SOCAL_logo.jpg</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WGCU Public Media (WGCU-TV)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1344</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WGCU Public Media</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Florida</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Fory Myers</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://wgcu.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KGNU-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1323</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KGNU-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Colorado</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Boulder</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.kgnu.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PBS Hawaii (KHET)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1748</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PBS Hawaii</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Hawaii</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Honolulu</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.pbshawaii.org/home/index.php</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KAKM (Alaska Public Media)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1702</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KAKM Alaska Public Media</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Alaska</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Anchorage</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.alaskapublic.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Detroit Public Television (aka DPTV and WTVS)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1786</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Detroit Public Television</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Michigan</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Wixom</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.dptv.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Maine Public Broadcasting</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1781</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Maine Public Broadcasting Network</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Maine</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Lewiston</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.mpbn.net/</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Maine Public Broadcasting Network is a statewide dual licensee providing both television and radio service throughout the state of Maine. MPBN’s television service is also available in the Canadian maritime provinces and Quebec.&#13;Today’s MPBN is a result of a 1992 merger between Lewiston, Maine based WCBB and Orono, Maine based WMEB. &#13;WCBB TV was founded by Colby College, Bates College and Bowdoin College and signed on as the first educational television service in Maine on November 13, 1961. It served the southern and western parts of the state and the studio was based in Lewiston.&#13;WMEB TV was founded by the University of Maine system and first went to air on October 7, 1963. Among its programs was the “Friendly Giant” and “History with Herb Hake”.  In 1964, transmitters are constructed in Presque Isle and Calais bringing educational television to northern and eastern Maine.  In 1974 another transmitter is built to serve southern Maine. This group of stations becomes known as the Maine Public Broadcasting Network in 1971. Based on the University of Maine campus it moves to larger facilities in Bangor in 1987.&#13;In 1970, MPBN launched WMEH-FM, Maine’s first public radio service.&#13;WCBB and MPBN collaborated many times over the years but finally merged to form a single entity in July of 1992. After several name changes in the ensuing years, MPBN is chosen to represent both the television and radio services.&#13;Five television transmitters and seven radio transmitters form the statewide backbone of the transmission system. MPBN television provides one HD and three SD channels in its digital broadcast stream: regular PBS programming with occasional local productions (HD), MPBN Create (SD), MPBN World (SD) and a fourth channel which is used for seasonal coverage of the Maine Legislature (SD).</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The News Machine, and its French language counterpart La Machine Magique - began in 1974. This weekly half-hour was a news program aimed at grade school students. The French version was added to serve the French Acadian population of far northern Maine. Both series ran in the mid 1970s.&#13;La Bonne Aventure - a 20 episode series devoted to French heritage received national distribution and acclaim in 1976. In 1979 MPBN broadcast the Maine State High School Basketball Tournaments. This annual production continues to this day and features 44 live games from three locations played over the course of 2 weeks each February and garners some of the highest ratings of the year. &#13;Maine Watch - launched in 1987. This weekly public affairs program ran until 2013 and included as one of its hosts the future Maine Governor and U.S. Senator Angus King. Maine Capitol Connection, daily live coverage of Maine’s legislative activities, began on February 6, 2013 and ran for two legislative sessions. </Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">MPBN_logo.jpg</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WPBS</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1823</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WPBS</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">New York</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Watertown</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.wpbstv.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WSKG Public Broadcasting</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1813</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WSKG Public Broadcasting</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">New York</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Vestal</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.wskg.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">New Jersey Network</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1809</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">New Jersey Network</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">New Jersey</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Trenton</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.njtvonline.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Wyoming PBS (KCWC)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1898</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Wyoming PBS</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Wyoming</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Riverton</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.wyomingpbs.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WDIY-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1589</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WDIY</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Pennsylvania</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Bethlehem</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://wdiy.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WLVT (PBS39)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1841</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PBS39</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Pennsylvania</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Bethlehem</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.wlvt.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WRFA-LP</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">4785</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WRFA</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">New York</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Jamestown</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.wrfalp.com/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KCTS 9</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1890</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KCTS 9</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Washington</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Seattle</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://kcts9.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WHUT-TV (Howard University Television)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1731</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WHUT Howard University Television</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">DC</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Washington</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.whut.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WVIA</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1848</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WVIA Public Media</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Pennsylvania</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Pittston</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.wvia.org/</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">For almost 50 years WVIA Public Media offers broad-appeal programming for the entire family to enjoy both on WVIA-FM and WVIA-TV. From award winning Original Documentary Films, NPR News plus powerful &amp; insightful Regional Programming WVIA inspires &amp; captivates its listeners, online users and viewers. WVIA Public Media is proud to serve northeastern Pennsylvania, the Central Susquehanna Valley and beyond. WVIA Public Media is a catalyst, convener and educator, using media, partnerships, ideas and programs to advance the best attributes of an enlightened society.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:Index="9"><Data ss:Type="String">wvia_logo.jpg</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KWSU/KTNW (Northwest Public Television)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1889</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Northwest Public Television</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Washington</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Pullman</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.nwptv.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">New Hampshire Public Television</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1808</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">New Hampshire Public Television</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">New Hampshire</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Durham</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.nhptv.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WIAA-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1451</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WIAA</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Michigan</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Interlochen</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://interlochenpublicradio.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WERU-FM (WERU Community Radio)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1430</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WERU Community Radio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Maine</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">East Orland</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">https://weru.org/</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">On May 1, 1988, after eight years of planning and work by an highly dedicated group of volunteers, WERU began broadcasting at 89.9 FM from the top of Blue Hill Mountain on the coast of Maine. Noel Paul Stookey (of Peter, Paul and Mary fame) was the station's first benefactor and from whose converted chicken coop, affectionately known as &quot;The Henhouse,&quot; WERU first broadcast. &#13;In 1997 the station moved to its current location on U.S. Route 1 in East Orland, centrally located in the middle of the radio station’s signal area.&#160;&#13;WERU is noncommercial and independent, and from its inception it has been a grassroots, volunteer-powered and listener-supported community radio service.&#13;WERU offers over 50 genres of music as well as a wide variety of national and local news, public affairs and short spoken-word features.  Almost all of WERU’s local content is produced by volunteers from the community. &#13;WERU is a member of the National Federation of Community Broadcasters and Maine Association of Broadcasters.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:Index="9"><Data ss:Type="String">were_logo.tiff</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">• WERU Program Director Dave Piszcz with Phillip Berrigan from Prison (two parts - cpb-aacip-301-63fxpvmr and cpb-aacip-301-1937pxmk)&#13;• Poems I Like - May Sarton (cpb-aacip-301-214mw8jg)&#13;• Poems I Like - Phillip Booth (cpb-aacip-301-71ngf87b)&#13;• WERU Volunteer Deb Suran Interviews Oscar Brand (cpb-aacip-301-75dbs300)</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WUSF</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1744</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WUSF</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Florida</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Tampa</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.wusf.usf.edu/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WFCR</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1438</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WFCR</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Massachusetts</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Amherst</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://nepr.net/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KGLT-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">4608</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KGLT</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Montana</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Bozeman</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.kglt.net/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Public Broadcasting Atlanta</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1746</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Public Broadcasting Atlanta</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Georgia</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Atlanta</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.pba.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WEDU Florida Public Media</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1742</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WEDU Florida Public Media</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Florida</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Tampa</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.wedu.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Idaho Public Television</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1750</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Idaho Public Television</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Idaho</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Boise</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://idahoptv.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WTIP (North Shore Community Radio)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">4602</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WTIP North Shore Community Radio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Minnesota</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Grand Marais</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.wtip.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KGTF (PBS Guam)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1900</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PBS Guam</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Guam</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Mangilao</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://pbsguam.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Colorado Public Television</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1723</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Colorado Public Television</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Colorado</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Denver</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.cpt12.org/</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Originally known as KBDI Channel 12, Colorado Public Television (CPT12) is a unique civic resource and one of the country’s first alternative public television services. CPT12 provides important local, national and international programming services that are otherwise not available in Colorado.&#13;KBDI began operations in Broomfield, Colorado, with transmitting facilities on Squaw Mountain in Clear Creek County. At 11,500 feet, the site remains the highest of any full-power television station in the nation. From there, KBDI began serving first the Denver Metro area, and then the entire Colorado Front Range.&#13;Today, Colorado Public Television has grown to serve 85 percent of the state’s population. Ongoing improvements to its transmitters and wider digital carriage on cable and satellite systems are extending the station's reach in almost every direction across the state. Beyond Denver and the Front Range, CPT12 is increasingly received in various Western Slope and Eastern Plains communities, ever broadening its service throughout Colorado.&#13;Since 2003, the station has offered digital programming on three multicast channels. Today, these three channels include CPT12's flagship signal (12.1), a diverse mix of local, national and international programming and infused with quality PBS shows; CPT12+ (12.2), the best of independently produced documentaries, music, travel, exercise, cooking, public affairs and more; and MHz Worldview (12.3), a lineup of programs from around the world, including world news, foreign affairs, international mysteries, world music, sports, and foreign films.&#13;Frequently stretching the boundaries of public television, the station has been called many things – progressive, provocative, experimental, controversial, outrageous, courageous and more as it has worked to illuminate key social issues, and provide a platform for the underserved.&#160; &#160;CPT12 has always championed experimentation, creativity, new ideas and high broadcasting standards – all while working on a shoestring budget.&#160; Today, CPT12 maintains its independent spirit, even as it explores new media outlets, expands its mission and deepens its community involvement.&#13;Described as “the little station that could” by the Denver Post, Colorado Public Television remains lean and light on its feet – a small, frugal station that continues to deliver programming that is relevant, informative, entertaining and thought-provoking.&#13;Colorado Public Television's tagline, “World View, Community Voice,” represents the station's mission, programming choices, community activities and engagement with its Colorado constituents. A global perspective combined with local conversations will continue to be CPT12's guide into the future.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Colorado Inside Out&#13;Sounds on 29th&#13;Studio 12&#13;Tierra O Muerte: Land Or Death - 1991 Alfred I. duPont-Columbia Award&#13;Stories of Elyria - 1992 Regional Emmy for Best Documentary&#13;Everything Has A Spirit - 1994 First Place Documentary Award, Indian Film and Video Competition&#13;Snapshots from the DNC - 2008 Colorado Broadcasters Association Award of Excellence for Best News or Public Affairs Special&#13;Colorado Inside Out “Circa 1858” and Studio 12 “Sudan” (tie winners) - 2009 Regional Emmy Award for Best Interview/Discussion Program&#13;Studio 12 “Back to Sudan” - 2009 Colorado Broadcasters Association Award of Excellence for Best News or Public Affairs Special&#13;Allen True’s West - 2009 Colorado Broadcasters Association Certificate of Merit for Best Mini-Documentary or Series&#13;Colorado Inside Out “Circa 1959” - 2010 Regional Emmy Award for Best Interview/Discussion Program&#13;Sandzen: Ecstacy of Color - 2010 Colorado Broadcasters Association Award of Excellence for Best Mini-Documentary or Series&#13;Studio 12 “Return to Iwo Jima” - 2010 Colorado Broadcasters Association Award of Excellence for Best News or Public Affairs Special&#13;Colorado Inside Out “Circa 1935” - 2010 Colorado Broadcasters Association Certificate of Merit for Best News &amp; Public Affairs Special / 2011 Regional Emmy Award for Best Interview/Discussion Program&#13;Rex Ray: How to Make a Rex Ray - 2010 Colorado Broadcasters Association Certificate of Merit for Best Mini-Documentary or Series&#13;Sounds on 29th - 2012 Colorado Broadcasters Association Certificate of Merit for Best Mini-Documentary or Series&#13;Studio 12 &quot;Aurora Theater Shooting&quot; - 2012 Colorado Broadcasters Association Award of Excellence for Best Public Affairs Special Category&#13;Studio 12 &quot;Honoring America's War Heroes&quot; - 2012 Colorado Broadcasters Association Certificate of Merit for Best News Special/Public Affairs Special&#13;</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">colorado_pt_logo.jpg</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WUMB-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1441</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WUMB</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Massachusetts</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Boston</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.wumb.org</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WUMB-FM is a non-commercial radio station licensed to the University of Massachusetts with studios at the UMass Boston Campus, as the central hub for a network of eight public radio stations in Boston, Worcester, Falmouth, Newburyport, Stow, Marshfield, Orleans and Milford, New Hampshire. &#13;The Boston, Worcester and Falmouth stations all broadcast on 91.9FM.  The Newburyport, Stow and Marshfield stations can be heard on 91.7FM. The Orleans station can be heard on 1170AM, and Milford, New Hampshire on 88.7FM.&#13;All eight facilities simulcast the identical program schedule, which is produced from our studios located on the UMass Boston Campus.  The station’s 24 hour a day broadcast schedule reaches more than 80,000 unique listeners weekly in over 275 cities and towns in eastern and central Massachusetts, as well as Cape Cod and parts of Rhode Island, New Hampshire and Connecticut.  A webcast of our signal can also be heard live around the world through the internet, and we current reach over another 80,000 people from all 50 states and 147 different countries through our live stream.&#13;The Boston station, WUMB-FM, was the last station in the Metro-Boston area to be granted an FM license from the Federal Communications Commission.  It went on the air in 1982 with an all-volunteer announcing staff, moving to a professional staff in 1986, when it became a public radio affiliate of the Corporate for Public Broadcasting.  The station was the aspiration of a cadre of UMass Boston students in 1968, in what became a fourteen year campaign to get the station on the air.  The Worcester station, WBPR-FM, was purchased in 1993 from Worcester county Christian Broadcasting, which owned a permit to construct the station, but had never actually built it.  The Falmouth station, WFPB-FM, was developed with the help of an expansion funding grant from CPB and wen on the air in 1996.  The Orleans station was a donation from GramCam Communications in 1998, and the Newburyport station was built with the help of a grant from the U.S. Department of Commerce in 2001.&#13;WUMB-FM is committed to providing unique program offerings.  It is the country’s foremost radio station for folk and roots music, largely airing a mix including Singer/Songwriter, Blues, Celtic, Americana, Bluegrass and more.  During the weekends, the station is a cultural center for traditional Folk, Celtic and International music, as well as our public affairs show, Commonwealth Journal.&#13;WUMB also sponsors and operates 2 one week summer music camps for adults, as well as a weekend music getaway as well, geared toward furthering the participants’ musical skill.   WUMB is actively involved in several community engagement projects throughout the year.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Commonwealth Journal&#13;Summer Acoustic Music Week/Winter Acoustic Music Weekend&#13;WUMB Member Concerts and Events&#13;Student internet radio station (The Beacon Radio)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WUMB_logo.jpg</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUOW Puget Sound Public Radio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1658.1</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUOW Puget Sound Public Radio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Washington</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Seattle</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://kuow.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KET - The Kentucky Network</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1775</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KET - The Kentucky Network</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Kentucky</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Lexington</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.ket.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WFMU</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">4857</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WFMU</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">New Jersey</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Jersey City</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://wfmu.org/</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WFMU first went on the air in April 1958, then a part of Uppsala College in East Orange, New Jersey. Shortly before Uppsala's bankruptcy filing and closure on May 31, 1995, a group of station executives, personnel, and supporters formed Auricle Communications and bought the license from the college, making it a fully independent radio station. In August 1998 the station's studios and offices were relocated to a Jersey City facility purchased with listener donations. WFMU now broadcasts terrestrially and online. It has been the subject of various articles, [books][http://www.amazon.com/The-Best-LCD-Writing-WFMU-FM/dp/1568987153], and even a [film][http://www.wfmuthemovie.com/]</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Aircheck - An hour of radio ghosts recaptured: once in a lifetime occurrences and remembrances (some from WFMU's own archives). This is no mere nostalgia trip; Aircheck seeks out some of the more unusual and unpredictable moments and personalities in radio that probably wouldn't get attention anywhere else.&#160;(notable episode: Oct 2, 2003: Daniel Johnston &amp; Yo La Tengo)&#13;The Hound - James &quot;The Hound&quot; Marshall playing what he considers good music; mostly &quot;Weird old records. Most of the stuff I like is just this really old R &amp; B and Rockabilly, old instrumentals &#45;- stuff like that.&quot;&#160;(notable episode: Mar 29, 1986: Hasil Adkins)&#13;Radio Thrift Shop - Host Laura Cantrell scours the bargain bins, church bazaars and yard sales for those forgotten rekkids of all RPM. Often scratchy, swingy and stringy.&#160;(notable episode: Jun 12, 2004: Baby Gramps)&#13;A Rough Mix with Steinski - A big record collection, a long memory, and a short fuse.&#160;(notable episode: Jun 20, 2014: monologues)&#13;Greasy Kid Stuff - A show of music for children of all ages.&#160;(notable episode: May 27, 2006: Pirates, robots, tap-dancing)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WFMU_logo.jpg</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WBLV-FM (Blue Lake Public Radio)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1455</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Blue Lake Public Radio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Michigan</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Twin Lake</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://bluelake.org/radio/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Pioneer Public Television</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1793</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Pioneer Public Television</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Minnesota</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Appleton</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.pioneer.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Radio Bilingue</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1293</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Radio Bilingue</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">California</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Fresno</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://radiobilingue.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Southern Oregon Public Television (KSYS/KFTS)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1839</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Southern Oregon Public Television</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Oregon</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Medford</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.soptv.org/</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">In 1965, Oregon Educational Broadcasting (OEB), forerunner of Oregon Public Broadcasting (OPB), persuaded the Federal Communications Commission (FCC) to reassign channel 8 from Brookings to Medford. OEB intended to make channel 8 the third station in its television network, which at that time included flagship KOAC-TV in Corvallis and KOAP-TV (now KOPB-TV) in Portland. Southern Oregon was the only region of the state without public television. However, OEB backed out after a protracted battle with several commercial applicants. The license eventually went to Liberty Television, owners of KEZI-TV in Eugene.&#13;The owners of the two commercial stations in the area, Bill Smullin of KTVM-TV (now KOBI) and Ray Johnson of KMED-TV (now KTVL), helped a new nonprofit corporation, Southern Oregon Educational Company (SOEC), buy the channel 8 construction permit from Liberty. They also pledged payments of $50,000 once the station signed on. Getting the funds to sign on proved more difficult than expected. With the FCC permit about to run out, KSYS went on the air on January 17, 1977 with the strongest signal of any station in the region, at 191,000 watts. This was still not enough to cover Klamath Falls, and SOEC (later renamed Southern Oregon Public Television, Inc.) immediately applied for another station to cover that region. However, it took 12 more years before KFTS went on the air in January 1989.&#13;The two stations are the only public television stations in the state not affiliated with OPB, but occasionally air some of OPB's programs.&#13;There are also the &quot;Presenting Station&quot; for several national programs including Tommy Emmanuel and Jesse Cook pledge specials.  We also present the series Sierra Center Stage and Music Gone Public.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Immense Possibilities&#13;Souther Oregon Town Hall&#13;Student Showcase</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">SOPTV_logo.jpg</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUSP-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1315</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUSP-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">California</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Santa Cruz</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.kusp.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KCPT (KCPT Public Television 19)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1799</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KCPT</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Missouri</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Kansas City</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.kcpt.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WHRO</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1886</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WHRO</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Virginia</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Norfolk</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://whro.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Maryland Public Television</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1783</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Maryland Public Television</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Maryland</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Owings Mills</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.mpt.org/</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">In 1966, an act of the Maryland Legislature established the Maryland Educational-Cultural Television Commission, the governance body of what became known as the Maryland Center for Public Broadcasting and, later, Maryland Public Television. Ground was broken for a headquarters and studio facility in suburban Baltimore County’s community of Owings Mills on June 5, 1968, and the center went on the air on October 5, 1969.  The founding executive director, Dr. Frederick Breitenfeld, Jr., already a leading figure in public broadcasting at the time of his appointment, served as chief executive for 17 years.&#13;The center was established as a nonprofit, state-licensed public television network and member of the Public Broadcasting Service (PBS).  The state license required statewide reach, and so six towers across the enabled MPT to get its then-analog signal to all corners of Maryland and into contiguous states and the District of Columbia.  In 1976, the center initiated its first satellite communications project, linking two universities in a law school moot court competition some 22,300 miles in space.&#13;The 1970s and 1980s saw the introduction of an astounding variety of center-produced historical dramas, how-to programs, nature, and music offerings in addition to educational and cultural programming. It was during this time that several MPT series enjoyed their premieres and what would become decades-long popularity among viewers locally and nationally.  MPT was rewarded for is production prowess with dozens of Emmy® Awards (four of them national and the remainder regional) along with an impressive list of other major broadcasting honors.&#13;In 1984, the name Maryland Center for Public Broadcasting gave way to Maryland Public Television. In 2004, MPT began broadcasting in both analog and digital formats until digital-only transmission started in 2009.  In 2007, MPT introduced V-me, a 24-hour Spanish language channel, which joined MPT’s two other digital channels, the primary MPT-HD and secondary channel MPT2, in the daily programming lineup. &#13;MPT has been a pioneer in the production, delivery and dissemination of pre-K-12 educational resources and online courses. The award-winning education website Thinkport.org, launched in 2003, offers high-quality lesson plans, digital media, learning games and resources for educators, schools, the child care population, and families.  &#13;Another MPT educational endeavor, started in the late 1960s, came out of the State Department of Education’s formation of a Division of Instructional Television.   ITV, as it was known, was awarded one-third of the Maryland Center for Public Broadcasting’s available production facilities, staff, and program schedule. By 1980-81 over 42% of Maryland teachers were using instructional television. &#13;In 1970, College of the Air debuted, as the center became the largest U.S. producer of telecourses for credit. Today, via Thinkport, the platform for learning has expanded to embrace online and mobile technologies, but MPT remains committed to being Maryland’s sole statewide educator just as it was in the 1970s and ‘80s.  &#13;Starting in 2007, the Corporation for Public Broadcasting funded MPT to participate in the the American Archive inventory of public media content. Working on a tight deadline of five months beginning in late summer and finishing in December 2011, an MPT team worked 3,500 hours and was able to inventory almost 48,000 assets.&#13;Today, under the leadership of CEO Larry D. Unger, MPT’s fifth president, some 140 staff members continue to produce award-winning local and national public television programs, to provide distinctive online content and community outreach initiatives, and to offer an impressive array of educational resources for children, teachers, families, and daycare providers across the state and nationally.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Wall $treet Week With Louis Rukeyser - 1972-2002; highlight was 1987 broadcast from London Stock Exchange to more than 300 U.S. PBS stations&#13;MotorWeek – 1981-present; television’s longest-running automotive series&#13;Our Street – groundbreaking MPT-produced drama focusing on then-described “Negro family life in West Baltimore”&#13;Crabs – 1984; half-hour comedy special live studio audience, numerous national and internat’l awards&#13;Consumer Survival Kit, 1973-79, more than 100 30-minute programs; series educated consumers; nationally distributed to PBS from 1974-79&#13;HodgePodge Lodge – 1970-76; 600 30-min. programs, nature series; the first privately underwritten, MPT-produced program; distributed nationally &#13;</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">MPT_logo.jpg</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Connecticut Public Broadcasting</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1727</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Connecticut Public Broadcasting Network</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Connecticut</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Hartford</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.cpbn.org/</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">In October 1962, the Connecticut Educational Television Corporation began broadcasting over station WEDH-TV (Channel 24) in black and white from the basement of the Trinity College Library in Hartford, Connecticut. In the beginning, motivated and eager individuals had a vision: to enrich people's lives through high-quality, non-commercial, educational programming. Institutions like Trinity College and the State of Connecticut supported this goal of reaching out to the community through public broadcasting.&#13;The station broadcast its first local children’s programming a few weeks after it went on the air, followed a month later by a biweekly local series highlighting the world of arts, entertainment and public affairs in the state. A mobile truck arrived in 1967, color in 1968, auctions in 1972, and pledge in 1973. By 1974, three additional stations across the state had joined WEDH-TV and CPTV was born. The statewide network earned its first Emmy Award in 1977, received its first satellite transmission in 1979, and taped its first national pledge special in 1985.&#13;The first public radio station in Connecticut signed on in June 1978, and soon Connecticut Public Radio (WNPR) joined CPTV to form what is now known as Connecticut Public Broadcasting. Initially airing primarily classical and radio music, WNPR now focuses on news and information. Together, the two community-supported, statewide public broadcasting networks are dedicated to serving Connecticut with a mix of educational, news, public affairs, children's and entertainment programming and services. &#13;Today, CPTV and WNPR reach the entire state of Connecticut – an estimated 550,000 television viewers and more than 240,000 radio listeners each week. Connecticut Public Broadcasting is the state’s only locally owned media organization producing TV, radio, print and Internet content for distribution to Connecticut’s wide-ranging and diverse communities.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Mundo Real (CPTV, 1976-1978) - One of the first television series to focus on a Puerto Rican family, Mundo Real was a Spanish-English bilingual educational children’s series aimed at ages 7-11. It was funded by four successive grants from the U.S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare.  A total of 39 episodes were produced. The series was syndicated to commercial and public television stations throughout the country, airing on at least 60 in 1978 and PBS aired episodes nationally in 1981.  &#13;Open Air New England / The Faith Middleton Show (WNPR, 1981-Present) - The two-time Peabody Award-winning Faith Middleton Show has been widely recognized for fostering insightful, thought-provoking conversation for more than 30 years. Faith offers her listeners some of the world's most fascinating people and subjects. The show has been inducted into the Connecticut Magazine Hall of Fame as “Best Local Talk Show.” &#13;Barney &amp; Friends (CPTV, 1992-2005) - For over a decade, CPTV co-produced Barney &amp; Friends for PBS. A CPTV executive thought Barney might be a good fit for television after renting a Barney video for his daughter. When it premiered in April 1992, the series was a huge hit, far more popular than anyone could have possibly imagined. &#13;CPTV UConn Women's Basketball (CPTV, 1994-2012) - CPTV was the TV broadcast home of the phenomenally successful UConn Women’s Basketball team for 18 years. With some of the consistently highest ratings and strongest membership levels of any program on public television for close to two decades, UConn Women’s Basketball on CPTV is considered by many to be the most successful local franchise in public television history. &#13;Infinity Hall Live (CPTV, 2011-Present) - Since 2011, CPTV has produced and distributed nationally to public television stations across the country this Emmy-award winning series that provides an all-access pass to engaging performances and backstage conversations with today’s most intriguing musical artists. It offers authentic and heartfelt performances taped at Infinity Music Hall, an acoustically perfect Victorian-era concert hall in Norfolk, CT. Artists featured on the series include The Barenaked Ladies, Joan Osborne, Fountains of Wayne, Tori Amos, and Wilson Phillips.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">cpbn_logo.jpeg</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KVCR</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1717</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KVCR</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">California</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">San Bernardino</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://kvcr.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUT Radio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1616</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUT Radio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Texas</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Austin</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://kut.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUVO-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1328</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUVO</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Colorado</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Denver</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://kuvo.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KEET</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1711</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KEET</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">California</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Eureka</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.keet.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">University of Maryland</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NCSG0150</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">University of Maryland</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Maryland</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">College Park</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.lib.umd.edu/special</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:Index="9"><Data ss:Type="String">UMD_logo.doc</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KSJN-FM (Minnesota Public Radio)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1466</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Minnesota Public Radio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Minnesota</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">St. Paul</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://minnesota.publicradio.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">South Carolina Network (SCETV) (WRLK)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1851</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">South Carolina ETV</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">South Carolina</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Columbia</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.scetv.org/</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">South Carolina Educational Television began in the library of a high school in 1958.  A teacher shortage in French and algebra was solved by sending teachers via closed circuit television to other schools.  The circuits eventually extended statewide, and into broadcast by 1963.  In 1972, the network expanded again into public radio as a member of NPR.  Today, South Carolina ETV consists of 11 TV transmitters and 8 radio transmitters carrying five different services statewide.  Through ETV Streamline, ETV provides classroom content via the internet with safe, standards-based curriculum.&#13;First an affiliate of NET (National Educational Television) and now a member of  PBS, South Carolina ETV became a producer and presenter of national public television programs, including Firing Line with William F. Buckley, Jr., The Magic School Bus, NatureScene, and A Chef’s Life (Peabody winner).  The ETV Radio service produces national series Marian McPartland’s Piano Jazz (Peabody winner), Song Travels with Michael Feinstein, Chamber Music from Spoleto Festival USA (international distribution), and World of Opera.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:Index="9"><Data ss:Type="String">scetv_logo.jpg</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WGBH</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1784.2</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WGBH</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Massachusetts</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Boston</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.wgbh.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WNYC-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1527</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WNYC</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">New York</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">New York</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">http://www.wnyc.org/</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
  </Table>
  <WorksheetOptions xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:excel">
   <Print>
    <ValidPrinterInfo/>
    <HorizontalResolution>-4</HorizontalResolution>
    <VerticalResolution>-4</VerticalResolution>
   </Print>
   <PageLayoutZoom>0</PageLayoutZoom>
   <Selected/>
   <FreezePanes/>
   <FrozenNoSplit/>
   <SplitHorizontal>1</SplitHorizontal>
   <TopRowBottomPane>82</TopRowBottomPane>
   <ActivePane>2</ActivePane>
   <Panes>
    <Pane>
     <Number>3</Number>
    </Pane>
    <Pane>
     <Number>2</Number>
     <ActiveRow>121</ActiveRow>
     <ActiveCol>4</ActiveCol>
    </Pane>
   </Panes>
   <ProtectObjects>False</ProtectObjects>
   <ProtectScenarios>False</ProtectScenarios>
  </WorksheetOptions>
 </Worksheet>
 <Worksheet ss:Name="Check_list">
  <Table ss:ExpandedColumnCount="7" ss:ExpandedRowCount="125" x:FullColumns="1"
   x:FullRows="1" ss:StyleID="s261" ss:DefaultColumnWidth="65"
   ss:DefaultRowHeight="15">
   <Column ss:StyleID="s261" ss:AutoFitWidth="0" ss:Width="344"/>
   <Column ss:StyleID="s260" ss:AutoFitWidth="0" ss:Width="135"/>
   <Column ss:StyleID="s261" ss:AutoFitWidth="0" ss:Width="298"/>
   <Column ss:StyleID="s261" ss:AutoFitWidth="0" ss:Width="126" ss:Span="2"/>
   <Row ss:StyleID="s259">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">value from pbcoreAnnotation @annotationType=&quot;organization&quot;</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s260"><Data ss:Type="String">AMS_CPB_id</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Full Display Name</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">history of station</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">significant productions</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">logo filename</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Notes</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KNME</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1810</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KNME</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WFMU</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">4857</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WFMU</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Connecticut Public Broadcasting</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1727</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Connecticut Public Broadcasting</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WFYI-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1388</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WFYI-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WOSU Public Media</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1832</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WOSU Public Media</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Louisiana Public Broadcasting</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1777</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Louisiana Public Broadcasting</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Colorado Public Television</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1723</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Colorado Public Television</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KOCE/PBS SoCal</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1710</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KOCE/PBS SoCal</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KWSO-FM (Warm Springs Community Radio)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">4502</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KWSO-FM (Warm Springs Community Radio)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Maine Public Broadcasting</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1781</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Maine Public Broadcasting</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">UNC-TV</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1824</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">UNC-TV</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Twin Cities Public Television (KTCA-TV)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1797</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Twin Cities Public Television (KTCA-TV)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WGBY</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1784</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WGBY</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Wisconsin Public Radio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1896.2</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Wisconsin Public Radio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Need to edit logo</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WJCT-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1347</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WJCT-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WBRA-TV</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1888</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WBRA-TV</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Ozarks Public Broadcasting (KOZK/KOZJ)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1801</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Ozarks Public Broadcasting (KOZK/KOZJ)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WUMB-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1441</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WUMB-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WYSU 88.5 FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1571</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WYSU 88.5 FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WCNY</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">1822</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WCNY</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KNBA-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1254</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KNBA-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Southern Oregon Public Television (KSYS/KFTS)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1839</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Southern Oregon Public Television (KSYS/KFTS)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Rocky Mountain PBS (KRMA)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1724</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Rocky Mountain PBS (KRMA)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Maryland Public Television</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1783</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Maryland Public Television</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WVIA</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1848</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WVIA</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:Index="6"><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:Height="409">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WERU-FM (WERU Community Radio)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1430</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WERU-FM (WERU Community Radio)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:Index="6"><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s257"><Data ss:Type="String">Significant program are assets from AMS, need to figure out display.• WERU Program Director Dave Piszcz with Phillip Berrigan from Prison (two parts - cpb-aacip-301-63fxpvmr and cpb-aacip-301-1937pxmk)&#13;• Poems I Like - May Sarton (cpb-aacip-301-214mw8jg)&#13;• Poems I Like - Phillip Booth (cpb-aacip-301-71ngf87b)&#13;• WERU Volunteer Deb Suran Interviews Oscar Brand (cpb-aacip-301-75dbs300)</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WQED-TV</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1846</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WQED-TV</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:Index="6"><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Prairie Public Broadcasting</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1826</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Prairie Public Broadcasting</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:Index="6"><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">South Carolina Network (SCETV) (WRLK)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1851</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">South Carolina Network (SCETV) (WRLK)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:Index="6"><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">University of Maryland</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NCSG0150</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">University of Maryland</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:Index="6"><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Illinois Public Media  (WILL)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1760</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Illinois Public Media  (WILL)</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUHF-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">1627</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUHF-FM</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Vegas PBS (KLVX)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">1806</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Vegas PBS (KLVX)</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WCTE</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="Number">1864</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WCTE</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KEXP-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1658.2</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KEXP-FM</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WYSO-FM (WYSO Public Radio)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1570</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WYSO-FM (WYSO Public Radio)</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Pacifica Radio Archives</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NCSG43</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Pacifica Radio Archives</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Wisconsin Public Television (WHA-TV)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1896</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Wisconsin Public Television (WHA-TV)</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Iowa Public Television</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1770</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Iowa Public Television</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Community Television Foundation of South Florida, Inc</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1737</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Community Television Foundation of South Florida, Inc</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Vermont Public Television</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1882</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Vermont Public Television</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Chicago Public Radio (WBEZ-FM) and Vocalo.org</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1370</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Chicago Public Radio (WBEZ-FM) and Vocalo.org</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KQED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1720</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KQED</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUCB (Unalaska Community Broadcasting/KIAL)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1275</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUCB (Unalaska Community Broadcasting/KIAL)</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Mississippi Public Broadcasting</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1798</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Mississippi Public Broadcasting</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WSIU Public Broadcasting</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1752</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WSIU Public Broadcasting</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WFIU-FM (Public Radio from Indiana University)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1383</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WFIU-FM (Public Radio from Indiana University)</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Thirteen - New York Public Media (WNET)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1817</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Thirteen - New York Public Media (WNET)</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WVIZ/ideastream</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1831</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WVIZ/ideastream</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WNED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1815</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WNED</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1881</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUED</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KVIE</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1716</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KVIE</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KRCB</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1709</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KRCB</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Cincinnati Public Radio (WGUC-FM, WMUB-FM, WVXU-FM)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1559</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Cincinnati Public Radio (WGUC-FM, WMUB-FM, WVXU-FM)</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUSC-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1297</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUSC-FM</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Nine Network of Public Media (formerly KETC)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1800</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The Nine Network of Public Media (formerly KETC)</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Arkansas Educational TV Network (AETN)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1708</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Arkansas Educational TV Network (AETN)</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Mountain Lake PBS (WCFE)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1818 </Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Mountain Lake PBS (WCFE)</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KDLG-AM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1259</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KDLG-AM</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KYUK</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1703</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KYUK</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WMHT</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1820</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WMHT</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">x</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WRNI (Rhode Island Public Radio)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">4844</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WRNI (Rhode Island Public Radio)</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Appalshop, Inc. (WMMT and Appalshop Films)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1419</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Appalshop, Inc. (WMMT and Appalshop Films)</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KMOS</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1802</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KMOS</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Film &amp;amp; Media Archive, Washington University in St. Louis</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">NCSG16</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Film and Media Archive, Washington University in St. Louis</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Oregon Public Broadcasting (OPB)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1840</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Oregon Public Broadcasting (OPB)</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WXPN-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1595</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WXPN-FM</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WTIU (Public Television from Indiana University)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1761</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WTIU (Public Television from Indiana University)</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WGVU Public TV &amp;amp; Radio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s258"><Data ss:Type="String">1789</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WGVU Public TV and Radio</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Iowa Public Radio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1393</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Iowa Public Radio</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">New Hampshire Public Radio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1502</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">New Hampshire Public Radio</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WXXI Public Broadcasting (WXXI-TV)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1531</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WXXI Public Broadcasting (WXXI-TV)</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KCAW-FM  (Raven Radio Foundation, Inc.)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1271</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KCAW-FM  (Raven Radio Foundation, Inc.)</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KXCI Community Radio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1283</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KXCI Community Radio</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Friends of WWOZ, Inc.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1427</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Friends of WWOZ, Inc.</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KDNA-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1653</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KDNA-FM</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WDVX-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">4721</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WDVX-FM</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WUFT-TV</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1735</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WUFT-TV</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WOJB-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1666</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WOJB-FM</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUNM (aka KNME-FM)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1507</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUNM (aka KNME-FM)</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Vermont Public Radio - WVPR</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1642</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Vermont Public Radio - WVPR</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WYCC-TV20 PBS Chicago</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1755</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WYCC-TV20 PBS Chicago</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WHYY</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1844</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WHYY</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WKAR</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1787</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WKAR</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WGCU Public Media (WGCU-TV)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1344</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WGCU Public Media (WGCU-TV)</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KGNU-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1323</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KGNU-FM</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PBS Hawaii (KHET)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1748</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">PBS Hawaii (KHET)</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KAKM (Alaska Public Media)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1702</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KAKM (Alaska Public Media)</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Detroit Public Television (aka DPTV and WTVS)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1786</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Detroit Public Television (aka DPTV and WTVS)</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WPBS</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1823</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WPBS</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WSKG Public Broadcasting</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1813</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WSKG Public Broadcasting</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">New Jersey Network</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1809</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">New Jersey Network</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Wyoming PBS (KCWC)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1898</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Wyoming PBS (KCWC)</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WDIY-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1589</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WDIY-FM</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WLVT (PBS39)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1841</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WLVT (PBS39)</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WRFA-LP</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">4785</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WRFA-LP</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KCTS 9</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1890</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KCTS 9</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WHUT-TV (Howard University Television)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1731</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WHUT-TV (Howard University Television)</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KWSU/KTNW (Northwest Public Television)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1889</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KWSU/KTNW (Northwest Public Television)</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">New Hampshire Public Television</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1808</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">New Hampshire Public Television</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WIAA-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1451</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WIAA-FM</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WUSF</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1744</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WUSF</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WFCR</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1438</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WFCR</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KGLT-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">4608</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KGLT-FM</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Public Broadcasting Atlanta</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1746</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Public Broadcasting Atlanta</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WEDU Florida Public Media</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1742</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WEDU Florida Public Media</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Idaho Public Television</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1750</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Idaho Public Television</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WTIP (North Shore Community Radio)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">4602</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WTIP (North Shore Community Radio)</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KGTF (PBS Guam)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1900</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KGTF (PBS Guam)</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUOW Puget Sound Public Radio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1658.1</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUOW Puget Sound Public Radio</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KET - The Kentucky Network</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1775</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KET - The Kentucky Network</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WBLV-FM (Blue Lake Public Radio)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1455</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WBLV-FM (Blue Lake Public Radio)</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Pioneer Public Television</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1793</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Pioneer Public Television</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Radio Bilingue</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1293</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Radio Bilingue</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUSP-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1315</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUSP-FM</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KCPT (KCPT Public Television 19)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1799</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KCPT (KCPT Public Television 19)</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WHRO</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1886</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WHRO</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KVCR</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1717</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KVCR</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUT Radio</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1616</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUT Radio</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUVO-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1328</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KUVO-FM</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KEET</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1711</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KEET</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KSJN-FM (Minnesota Public Radio)</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1466</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">KSJN-FM (Minnesota Public Radio)</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WGBH</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1784.2</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WGBH</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WNYC-FM</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">1527</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">WNYC-FM</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
  </Table>
  <WorksheetOptions xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:excel">
   <Print>
    <ValidPrinterInfo/>
    <HorizontalResolution>-4</HorizontalResolution>
    <VerticalResolution>-4</VerticalResolution>
   </Print>
   <PageLayoutZoom>0</PageLayoutZoom>
   <FreezePanes/>
   <FrozenNoSplit/>
   <SplitHorizontal>1</SplitHorizontal>
   <TopRowBottomPane>41</TopRowBottomPane>
   <ActivePane>2</ActivePane>
   <Panes>
    <Pane>
     <Number>3</Number>
    </Pane>
    <Pane>
     <Number>2</Number>
     <ActiveRow>61</ActiveRow>
     <ActiveCol>5</ActiveCol>
    </Pane>
   </Panes>
   <ProtectObjects>False</ProtectObjects>
   <ProtectScenarios>False</ProtectScenarios>
  </WorksheetOptions>
 </Worksheet>
</Workbook>
