male narrator:
IN THE SUMMER OF 1957,
LITTLE ROCK, ARKANSAS,
WAS CONSIDERED
A MODERATE SOUTHERN CITY.
THINGS WERE PRETTY NORMAL THERE
AS FAMILIES BEGAN TO PREPARE
FOR THE COMING SCHOOL YEAR.
HOWEVER, THE SHOCKING TRUTH
WAS THAT
THE CIVIL RIGHTS STRUGGLE
HAD COME TO LITTLE ROCK'S
CENTRAL HIGH SCHOOL.
PUZZLING IMAGES
OF THE ARKANSAS NATIONAL GUARD
CIRCLING THE SCHOOL,
THE LITTLE ROCK NINE BEING
BLOCKED FROM ENTRY,
ANGRY MOBS,
GOVERNOR FAUBUS MEETING
WITH PRESIDENT EISENHOWER,
THE 101ST AIRBORNE.
THE DRAMA PLAYING OUT
WAS A GREAT NEWS STORY
FOR THE DEVELOPING
TELEVISION INDUSTRY
AND GREAT DRAMA
FOR ALL JOURNALISTS.
THE EVENTS IN LITTLE ROCK
CAPTURED THE COVER
OFTIMEMAGAZINE
IN SEPTEMBER
AND OCTOBER OF 1957.
AS THESE IMAGES AND HEADLINES
SPILLED INTO LIVING ROOMS
ACROSS AMERICA AND THE WORLD,
LITTLE ROCK HAD BECOME
THE BATTLEFIELD
FOR THE CIVIL RIGHTS MOVEMENT.
THE STORY OF THAT YEAR,
THE 1957, 1958 CRISIS
AT CENTRAL HIGH
IS WELL-DOCUMENTED.
WE'RE HERE TO TELL YOU
OF ANOTHER STORY
OF LITTLE ROCK AND ITS PEOPLE,
THE FOLLOWING YEAR,
OF THE LITTLE ROCK DESEGREGATION
CRISIS.
>> EVERYONE SEEMS TO KNOW
ABOUT 1957, '58,
BUT NEWCOMERS TO ARKANSAS
AND THOSE BEYOND OUR BORDERS
AND MANY WHO ARE YOUNG
HAVE NEVER HEARD
OF THE LOST YEAR.
narrator: YOU MAY BE FAMILIAR
WITH THE PLIGHT
OF THE LITTLE ROCK NINE
AND THE STRUGGLES THAT YEAR
AT CENTRAL HIGH SCHOOL.
YOU MAY, HOWEVER,
BE UNAWARE OF THE STORY
OF THE LOST YEAR OF 1958, 1959
WHEN GOVERNOR FAUBUS
AND HIS SUPPORTERS
WORKED TO STOP INTEGRATION AGAIN
AND SUCCEEDED
FOR AN ENTIRE SCHOOL YEAR.
IN MAY OF 1958, ERNEST GREEN,
THE ONLY SENIOR
OF THE LITTLE ROCK NINE,
GRADUATED WITH HIS CLASS
FROM CENTRAL HIGH SCHOOL.
FINALLY, THE CRISIS
AT CENTRAL HIGH WAS OVER,
AND THE PEOPLE OF LITTLE ROCK
BREATHED A SIGH OF RELIEF.
BUT NOT FOR LONG.
>> AFTER THE YEAR
THAT THE LITTLE ROCK NINE
WENT TO CENTRAL
AND WE WERE AT HALL,
YOU KNOW, WE THOUGHT, WELL,
MAYBE NOW
WE'VE WEATHERED THE STORM
AND WE DON'T HAVE TO
HAVE LITTLE ROCK
BE IN THE BAD SPOTLIGHT ANYMORE.
AND THEN ALL OF A SUDDEN,
YOU KNOW, BAM.
IT HIT US AGAIN.
AND THE SCHOOLS WERE CLOSED,
AND IT WAS JUST
A TERRIBLE TIME.
>> THE SUMMER OF 1958
WE WERE EAGERLY LOOKING FORWARD
TO OUR JUNIOR YEAR
AT HORACE MANN.
LITTLE DID WE KNOW
THAT THERE WASN'T GOING TO BE
A JUNIOR YEAR.
BUT THAT'S WHAT WE
WERE LOOKING FORWARD TO,
THE MANY ACTIVITIES,
THE JUNIOR-SENIOR PROM,
AND THINGS OF THAT SORT.
>> GOVERNOR FAUBUS
AND THE CITIZENS COUNCIL
AT THAT TIME
I THINK IT WAS CALLED,
THEIR AGENDA WAS NOT THE AGENDA
THAT I WOULD HAVE CHOSEN.
>> AFTER HE MADE THE DECISION
TO DO WHAT HE DID
AT CENTRAL HIGH,
HIS POPULARITY JUST DOUBLED.
WE GOT MAIL BY THE TOE-SACKS
FULL IN SUPPORT OF HIM.
SO I THINK AT THAT POINT
HE REALIZED
THAT HE HAD A VERY GOOD CHANCE
TO WIN A THIRD TERM.
>> AFTER ORVAL FAUBUS WON HIS
THIRD NOMINATION FOR GOVERNOR,
AND WITH THAT VOTE
OF 75 OUT OF 75 COUNTIES,
BASICALLY, THREE EVENTS
IN THE SUMMER OF 1958
THAT ALLOWED
THE LOST YEAR TO HAPPEN.
THE FIRST ONE
WAS THAT THE SCHOOL BOARD
HAD FILED FOR A DELAY.
>> A NUMBER
OF BUSINESS LEADERS PERSUADED
A MAJORITY OF THE MEMBERS
OF THE SCHOOL BOARD
THAT THEY OUGHT TO GO BACK
TO THE FEDERAL COURT
AND ASK FOR A DELAY.
>> AND IN FILING FOR THAT DELAY
IN COOPER V. AARON,
THEY REQUESTED A 2 1/2 YEAR
DELAY OF FURTHER INTEGRATION.
>> THEY HAD TRIED TO INTEGRATE.
THEY HAD DEMONSTRATED
THAT IT WOULDN'T WORK
WITHOUT VIOLENCE
AND WITHOUT FEDERAL TROOPS
IN HERE
TO CONTROL THE SITUATION.
SO THEY SAID--THEY PETITIONED
THE FEDERAL JUDGE FOR A DELAY.
>> THE NAACP IMMEDIATELY
FOUGHT THAT DELAY.
AND THEN FINALLY FAUBUS' CALL
OF THE LEGISLATURE IN AUGUST
SET UP THE GROUNDWORK
FOR WHAT HE WOULD BE ABLE TO DO
WITH THE SCHOOLS
IN THE YEAR OF '58, '59.
narrator: DURING THE LOST YEAR,
OVER 3,600 HIGH SCHOOL STUDENTS,
BOTH BLACK AND WHITE,
WERE LOCKED OUT
OF THEIR PUBLIC HIGH SCHOOLS.
TEACHERS UNDER CONTRACT
FACED EMPTY CLASSROOMS
FOR THE ENTIRE YEAR.
>> IN MY MIND,
I THINK 95% OF THE STUDENTS,
POSSIBLY MORE THAN THAT,
WANTED TO GO TO SCHOOL
AND JUST WANTED THIS THING
TO KIND OF GET OVER WITH
AND HOPEFULLY
THAT IT WOULD BLEND IN.
I THINK THERE WERE A VERY SMALL
PERCENTAGE OF THE STUDENTS
THAT DID NOT WANT
TO SEE THIS THROUGH AT ALL
AND DID NOT CARE IF THEY
RECEIVED THE EDUCATION OR NOT,
THEY WOULD HAVE
JUST AS SOON LEFT.
I DID NOT
FALL INTO THAT CATEGORY.
>> THE BILLS THAT WERE PASSED
IN THE EXTRAORDINARY SESSION
OF THE SUMMER OF--
AUGUST OF 1958,
ALLOWED THE GOVERNOR
TO DO MANY THINGS.
ONE OF THE MOST IMPORTANT
THAT HAD TO DO WITH US
WAS HIS ABILITY TO CLOSE SCHOOLS
THREATENED WITH INTEGRATION.
THE SECOND ONE
WAS ABOUT FINANCES.
AND IT ALLOWED STATE MONEY
TO FOLLOW A STUDENT
TO WHATEVER ACCREDITED SCHOOL
THEY CHOSE
SO THAT STATE TAX MONEY
COULD ACTUALLY FOLLOW A STUDENT
TO A PRIVATE SCHOOL
AS LONG AS IT WAS ACCREDITED.
AND PROBABLY
THE THIRD IMPORTANT ISSUE
WAS THAT
IT THREATENED TEACHERS ALREADY
IN THE SUMMER OF 1958
BY ASKING ALL THE TEACHERS
AND STATE EMPLOYEES
TO SIGN DOCUMENTS
THAT SAID THAT YOU MUST LIST
EVERY ORGANIZATION
TO WHICH YOU BELONG.
narrator: THE UNITED STATES
SUPREME COURT
HAD MET ONLY THREE TIMES
IN ITS HISTORY
FOR A SPECIAL SESSION.
THE LOST YEAR CASE
WAS ONE OF THOSE THREE TIMES.
ON SEPTEMBER 12TH, IT ANNOUNCED
THAT INTEGRATION MUST PROCEED.
AND FAUBUS SWINGS INTO ACTION.
>> THE ELEMENTARY SCHOOLS
AND THE JUNIOR HIGH SCHOOLS
HAD OPENED.
THEY HAD OPENED
IN EARLY SEPTEMBER OF 1958.
BUT HIGH SCHOOL STUDENTS
WERE DELAYED
BECAUSE OF THE COURT CASE.
WHEN THE FEDERAL COURTS SAY,
"GO FORWARD WITH INTEGRATION,"
FAUBUS TAKES THE 16 BILLS
THAT ARE ON HIS DESK;
HE'S WAITING--HE'S WAITING
FOR THIS COURT DECISION.
HE SIGNS INTO LAW THE 16 BILLS.
HE PHONES THE SUPERINTENDENT
OF THE SCHOOLS AND SAYS
ALL HIGH SCHOOLS IN LITTLE ROCK,
BLACK AND WHITE,
WILL NOT OPEN ON MONDAY.
THEY WILL NOT OPEN.
>> THERE WAS THIS SENSE OF
DESTRUCTION OF LIFE.
AND I OFTEN SAY THAT I
CONSIDERED WHAT ORVAL FAUBUS DID
TO BE A PERSONAL ATTACK ON ME.
THIS WASN'T JUST POLITICAL.
THIS WASN'T JUST SOCIAL.
THIS WAS AN ATTACK
ON IRVING SPITZBERG.
AND I SAW MY WHOLE LIFE
DISAPPEARING IN FRONT OF ME.
narrator: THE FOUR HIGH SCHOOLS
IN LITTLE ROCK
THAT WERE CLOSED WERE:
CENTRAL HIGH SCHOOL,
WHERE THE CRISIS BEGAN
THE YEAR BEFORE;
HALL HIGH SCHOOL,
A NEW HIGH SCHOOL
BUILT IN WEST LITTLE ROCK
FOR WHITE STUDENTS;
HORACE MANN HIGH SCHOOL,
A NEW HIGH SCHOOL
BUILT IN EAST LITTLE ROCK
FOR BLACK STUDENTS;
AND LITTLE ROCK
TECHNICAL SCHOOL,
A SMALL TECHNICAL SCHOOL
FOR WHITE MALES.
>> IT WAS JUST
A STAGGERING BLOW TO ME.
IT WAS LIKE, "OH.
I MEAN, MY GOODNESS.
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?"
AND I FELT LIKE THAT THERE WAS
JUST NO HELP ANYWHERE.
THERE WAS NO 800 NUMBER TO CALL
AND GET ADVICE.
THERE WAS JUST NO HELP,
AND NO ONE, ACTUALLY NO ONE
REALLY KNEW WHAT TO DO.
narrator: ARKANSANS LOVE
THEIR FOOTBALL,
AND AS THE SCHOOL CLOSURES
HIT THE MEDIA,
THE PHONE STARTED RINGING
IN GOVERNOR FAUBUS' OFFICE.
IT DIDN'T TAKE LONG FOR SOMEONE
TO ASK THE INEVITABLE.
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT ABOUT FOOTBALL?
THE SCHEDULES WERE ALREADY SET.
AND SEVERAL OF THESE BOYS
WERE IN LINE FOR SCHOLARSHIPS
TO PLAY FOOTBALL IN COLLEGE.
>> THE LITTLE ROCK
CENTRAL TIGERS
WERE ARGUABLY
THE BEST FOOTBALL TEAM
IN THE NATION
FOR A TWO-YEAR PERIOD,
'57, '58 ESPECIALLY.
THEY HAD WON 33 GAMES IN A ROW
AT THE END OF MY JUNIOR YEAR,
WHICH WAS '57, '58,
AND AS WE ENTERED
OUR SENIOR YEAR,
WE WERE LOOKING VERY FORWARD
TO EXTENDING THAT RECORD.
>> FAUBUS ACTUALLY CALLED
VIRGIL BLOSSOM,
THE SUPERINTENDENT OF SCHOOLS,
AND SAID,
"I WANT YOU
TO PUT BACK IN FOOTBALL."
AND, ACCORDING
TO VIRGIL BLOSSOM'S BOOK,
HE SAYS, "SO WE RESTORED
TO THE STUDENTS OF LITTLE ROCK
"FOOTBALL.
"NO CLASSES, NO ACADEMIC WORK,
ONLY FOOTBALL."
>> THE FOOTBALL TEAM BEGAN
PRACTICE ON AUGUST THE 20TH,
AS THEY ALWAYS DID.
AND WE PLAYED OUR FIRST GAME
WHICH WAS A STRANGE EXPERIENCE
BECAUSE THE STANDS WERE FULL
AND THE CHEERLEADERS
AND THE FANS
BUT SCHOOL HADN'T OPENED,
WHICH SEEMED VERY, VERY ODD.
WE PLAYED OUR FIRST GAME,
AND THEN THE NEXT WEEK,
THE GAMES WERE CANCELLED.
AND AS A MATTER OF FACT,
WE ALL--
SEVERAL OF US
LOOKED AROUND AND THOUGHT,
YOU KNOW, "SCHOOLS DON'T LOOK
LIKE THEY'RE GONNA OPEN.
THERE'S A LOT GOING ON."
SO WE MADE A--
WE BEGAN TO TRANSFER.
AND QUITE A NUMBER OF US,
SIX OR SEVEN THAT WERE STARTERS
ON THE FOOTBALL TEAM,
TRANSFERRED
TO JACKSONVILLE HIGH SCHOOL.
BUT WE COULDN'T PLAY THERE
BECAUSE OF THE RULES
THAT YOU HAD TO
LIVE IN THE DISTRICT.
AND WE ALL FELT LIKE, WELL,
HALL HIGH WON'T DO VERY WELL
THIS YEAR IN FOOTBALL,
BUT AS IT TURNED OUT,
THEY WON
THE BIG NINE CHAMPIONSHIP
WITHOUT ALL OF US
IMPORTANT PLAYERS.
>> THE BAND MEMBERS, I REMEMBER,
THEY STILL ATTEND BAND PRACTICE,
AND THEY'D PRACTICE
OUT ON THE FIELD.
I REMEMBER
WHEN HORACE MANN'S BAND
PRACTICED ON CENTRAL HIGH'S
PRACTICE FIELD.
YOU KNOW, SO TO ME, THAT'S--
EVERYTHING WAS INTEGRATED
TO A DEGREE.
narrator: IT'S LATER
IN SEPTEMBER;
THE SCHOOLS ARE STILL CLOSED.
THE REFERENDUM VOTE IS COMING UP
TO DECIDE THE FATE
OF THE SCHOOLS.
AND THERE ARE ALL THESE
TEENAGERS AND THEIR FAMILIES
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHAT TO DO.
>> WELL, IN THE BEGINNING,
WHEN WE HEARD
THAT THE SCHOOLS
WERE GONNA BE CLOSED,
WE THOUGHT, WELL,
MAYBE FOR A DAY.
AND WE NEVER DREAMED
THAT IT COULD LAST A LONG TIME.
AND MY FATHER
WAS VERY, VERY ADAMANT
ABOUT THE SCHOOLS WILL OPEN,
AND THEY WILL OPEN SOON,
AND SO YOU'RE STAYING
RIGHT HERE.
>> AS FAR AS KNOWING
WHAT WAS GOING ON,
WE DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT WAS GOING ON.
WELL, WE DID
GET WIND OF THINGS LIKE THAT,
BUT IT WAS,
"WHY ARE THEY DOING THIS?"
THAT WAS MOSTLY
A QUESTION THAT WE ALL HAD.
narrator: AND WHAT WAS
THE SCHOOL BOARD DOING
ABOUT THE SITUATION?
>> THE SCHOOL BOARD
AT THAT TIME THOUGHT,
"WE HAVE TO DO SOMETHING."
MAYBE THE VOTERS OF LITTLE ROCK
WILL VOTE AGAINST THIS
AND WE WILL HAVE SCHOOL OPENING.
SO WHAT CAN WE DO
IN THE MEANTIME?
SO THEY WORKED WITH THE THREE
BRAND-NEW TELEVISION STATIONS
TO PROVIDE TELEVISION TEACHING.
AND THEY HIRED--
THEY DIDN'T HIRE;
THEY PULLED 15 WHITE TEACHERS
TO GO DOWN
TO THE TELEVISION STATIONS
AND PRESENT LESSONS
ON THE BASIC CLASSES.
SO THE INTERESTING THING
ABOUT THAT
IS THAT ANY STUDENT
THAT HAD A TV
COULD WATCH THOSE LESSONS.
SO IT ALLOWED BOTH BLACKS
AND WHITES TO HAVE SCHOOLING.
THEY PUT TENTH GRADE
AT ONE STATION,
11TH GRADE AT ANOTHER STATION,
AND 12TH GRADE
AT ANOTHER STATION.
>> I THINK I WAS MORE SAD
ABOUT LEAVING THAN MAD.
THEN, I THINK
AS THE YEARS GO BY,
YOU KIND OF GET MAD THINKING
WHAT DID HAPPEN
AND HOW REALLY UNAWARE,
AS A 17-YEAR-OLD, I WAS.
>> I WAS NOT AS ATTUNED
TO POLITICAL ISSUES AT THAT AGE.
THOSE KIND OF ISSUES
WERE NOT REALLY
DISCUSSED WITH US AS TEENAGERS.
narrator: BY LAW, FAUBUS
HAD TO HOLD A REFERENDUM VOTE
WITHIN 30 DAYS
OF THE SCHOOL CLOSURES.
THE ELECTION WAS HELD ON
THE LAST SATURDAY IN SEPTEMBER.
BUT THE BALLOT
DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING
ABOUT THE HIGH SCHOOLS
BEING CLOSED.
THE VOTERS WERE ASKED TO VOTE
FOR OR AGAINST INTEGRATION.
>> THEY HAD TO ACTUALLY
VOTE FOR INTEGRATION
IN ORDER
TO KEEP THE SCHOOLS OPEN.
AND THE VOTE WAS 19,000-PLUS
AGAINST 7,000-PLUS.
AND THE 19,000-PLUS
KEPT THE SCHOOLS CLOSED
RATHER THAN
HAVE THEM INTEGRATED.
SO THE VOTERS
OF LITTLE ROCK RESPONDED
IN JUST THE WAY THAT
ORVAL FAUBUS EXPECTED THEM TO.
>> THE EXPERIENCE WAS,
THIS IS JUST TERRIBLE.
THE WORLD'S GONNA SEE
HOW TERRIBLE IT IS,
BUT ALL THESE PEOPLE AROUND ME
ARE VOTING IN FAVOR OF IT.
AND, YOU KNOW, THIS WAS,
AGAIN, SURREAL
THAT ANYBODY COULD BELIEVE
WHAT THESE PEOPLE BELIEVED.
>> MY OPINION OF GOVERNOR FAUBUS
WAS PROBABLY DREADFULLY UNFAIR,
IN RETROSPECT,
BUT AT THE TIME,
I THOUGHT IT WAS HIS FAULT
THAT WE DID NOT HAVE
A SENIOR YEAR IN HIGH SCHOOL.
>> THE LITTLE ROCK NINE,
OF COURSE,
THIS AFFECTED THEM ALSO.
OF THE LITTLE ROCK NINE,
ERNEST GREEN HAD GRADUATED,
AND MISS TRICKEY
HAD BEEN EXPELLED
AND HAD MOVED TO NEW YORK
TO CONTINUE HER SCHOOLING THERE.
>> I WENT TO CENTRAL
IN GRADE 11,
WAS EXPELLED, AND LATER
WENT TO NEW YORK CITY TO SCHOOL,
BUT I CONSIDER THIS
PART OF MY LOST YEAR
BECAUSE IT'S THE AMERICAN
TRAGEDY.
>> SO THAT LEFT SEVEN
OF THE LITTLE ROCK NINE.
THEY, TOO, WERE LOCKED OUT
OF SCHOOL.
AND THEIR INTENTION--
SOME OF THEM
WERE INTENDING TO GO BACK
TO CENTRAL,
AND SO THEY TOO WERE LOCKED OUT
OF SCHOOL.
narrator: DURING THAT TIME
IN THE SOUTH,
SEPARATION OF THE RACES
WAS A WAY OF LIFE.
>> I CAN REMEMBER
BEING IN DOWNTOWN LITTLE ROCK
WITH MY MOTHER
AND PASSING BY A RESTAURANT
THAT HAD A BIG SALAD BOWL
IN THE WINDOW.
I SHALL NEVER FORGET THAT.
I WAS HUNGRY, AND I WANTED TO GO
INTO THAT RESTAURANT TO EAT.
AND SO I TOLD MY MOTHER
I WAS HUNGRY.
AND I SAID,
"THIS IS WHAT I WANT.
"I WANT SOME OF THE SALAD
THAT'S IN THE WINDOW,"
AND THAT'S WHEN SHE TOLD ME
THAT I COULDN'T GO THERE.
AND I SAID,
"BUT YOU GAVE ME SOME MONEY.
I HAVE SOME MONEY."
AND SHE SAID, "NO,
YOU CAN'T GO IN THAT RESTAURANT
BECAUSE YOU ARE BLACK."
>> I HAD BROUGHT
MY SCRAPBOOK WITH ME,
AND I WAS
GOING THROUGH SOME THINGS
TO MAKE SURE THAT
I WOULDN'T FORGET AND ALL THAT,
AND IN ONE OF
THE NEWSPAPER ARTICLES ABOUT US,
ON THE BACK SIDE,
I TURNED IT OVER,
AND THERE WAS THE OBITUARY
FOR LITTLE ROCK.
AND IT DAWNED ON ME
FOR THE VERY FIRST TIME
THERE'S THE OBITUARY,
BUT THEN ON THE SIDE,
IN LITTLE, SMALL ARTICLES,
IT SAID, "FUNERALS FOR NEGROES."
THEY WERE NOT EVEN INCLUDED
IN THE OBITUARY PAGE.
THEY HAD THEIR OWN LITTLE PLACE
WITH A LITTLE ARTICLE
THAT LARGE,
AND I NEVER KNEW THAT
TILL LAST NIGHT.
AND THAT'S THE SADNESS.
THAT'S WHAT
THEY HAD TO PUT UP WITH.
>> SEPARATION OF THE RACES
HAD EXISTED BY LAW,
LEGAL SEPARATION OF THE RACES,
SINCE THE LATE 1890s
IN ARKANSAS.
AND SO IT HAD BECOME
THE SYSTEM OF THE SOUTH,
THE JIM CROW SOUTH.
AND TO CHANGE ANYTHING
THAT INVASIVE
OF THE WHOLE SOCIETY
WOULD BE A SOCIAL, AN ECONOMIC,
EVERY KIND OF CHANGE
THAT YOU COULD IMAGINE.
SO WITH THE INTEGRATION
OF PUBLIC SCHOOLS
ENDORSED BY BROWN
VERSUS THE BOARD OF EDUCATION,
YOU WERE ASKING
THE COMMUNITIES OF THE SOUTH
TO CHANGE
THEIR ENTIRE LIFESTYLE.
narrator: ALL THE WHILE,
GOVERNOR FAUBUS
AND HIS FOLLOWERS HAD A PLAN.
THEY WERE HOPING
TO CONVERT PUBLIC SCHOOLS
AND PUBLIC SCHOOL TEACHERS
INTO A PRIVATE
SCHOOL CORPORATION.
>> IMMEDIATELY AFTER
THE ELECTION,
WHEN VOTERS VOTED
TO KEEP THE SCHOOLS CLOSED,
MAGICALLY WITHIN DAYS,
A LITTLE ROCK SCHOOL--
A PRIVATE
SCHOOL CORPORATION EMERGED.
THEIR PLAN WAS, ORIGINALLY,
TO LEASE
THE PUBLIC SCHOOL BUILDINGS
AND HIRE
THE PUBLIC SCHOOL TEACHERS.
narrator:
AND THE HIGH SCHOOL TEACHERS
WERE CAUGHT IN THE MIDDLE
OF THIS CONFLICT.
MANY WERE ASKED TO MOVE OVER
TO THE PRIVATE
SCHOOL CORPORATION
AND TEACH IN THE PRIVATE SCHOOLS
BEING FORMED.
>> JESS MATTHEWS CALLED
A FACULTY MEETING
DURING THE LOST YEAR
TO PRESENT TO TEACHERS
THE OPPORTUNITY
TO SIGN CONTRACTS TO TEACH
AT THE T.J. RANEY
PRIVATE SCHOOL.
I DIDN'T WANT
TO SIGN THAT CONTRACT.
I FELT VERY LOYAL
TO CENTRAL HIGH SCHOOL
AND TO THE LITTLE ROCK
SCHOOL DISTRICT,
AND I DID NOT
SIGN THAT CONTRACT.
>> SOME OF THE TEACHERS
WHO SIGNED THE CONTRACTS
FELT THAT THEY HAD BEEN
COMPELLED TO DO SO,
THAT THEY HAD NO CHOICE,
BECAUSE THEY WERE TOLD
THAT THIS IS THE ONLY WAY
WE CAN GET OUR STUDENTS
BACK IN SCHOOL.
YOU'LL BE IN THE SAME BUILDING
YOU'RE IN.
YOU'LL BE IN THE SAME CLASSROOM
YOU'LL HAVE THE SAME STUDENTS
THAT YOU HAD ASSIGNED TO YOU,
BUT YOU WILL BE TEACHING THEM
UNDER A PRIVATE
SCHOOL CORPORATION.
SO MANY OF THEM FELT COMFORTABLE
WITH SIGNING THAT DOCUMENT.
THE PLAN OF LEASING
PUBLIC SCHOOL BUILDINGS
TO PRIVATE SCHOOL CORPORATIONS
WOULD ALLOW FAUBUS
AND HIS SEGREGATIONIST FOLLOWERS
TO OPEN PRIVATE SCHOOLS,
AND THEREFORE THEY COULD
KEEP THEM SEGREGATED.
AND FAUBUS MADE A STATEMENT
ENDORSING THIS
USING AN 1875 LAW
ON THE BOOKS OF ARKANSAS
THAT ALLOWED THE LEASING
OF A PUBLIC SCHOOL BUILDING
TO A PRIVATE ENTITY.
narrator: HOWEVER,
ALL THE NEGOTIATIONS
ABOUT LEASING
THE PRIVATE SCHOOL BUILDINGS
AND HIRING
THE PUBLIC SCHOOL TEACHERS
WERE SHORT-LIVED.
>> THAT 24-HOUR PERIOD
WAS SO EMOTIONALLY DRAINING
FOR TEACHERS.
THEY GO HOME,
THEY'RE ALREADY WORRIED
ABOUT THE DECISION
THAT THEY'VE MADE,
AND THEY HEAR
A KNOCK AT THE DOOR,
AND THE FEDERAL MARSHALL
IS SERVING THEM
WITH A RESTRAINING ORDER
THAT SAYS
YOU WILL TEACH FOR NO ONE.
YOU--AT THIS MOMENT,
THE PUBLIC SCHOOLS ARE CLOSED,
THE PRIVATE SCHOOLS ARE CLOSED,
AND YOU WILL NOT
BE ABLE TO TEACH
FOR A PRIVATE
SCHOOL CORPORATION.
SO THERE WAS
A FEDERAL RESTRAINING ORDER,
AND THESE WERE DELIVERED
AT 10:00 AT NIGHT.
THE PUBLIC SCHOOL TEACHERS
WERE THEN PREVENTED
FROM SERVING
IN THOSE PRIVATE SCHOOLS.
>> WE HAD A HIGH REGARD
AND A RESPECT FOR HORACE MANN
BECAUSE WE FELT THAT WE HAD--
IT WAS PRETTY DIFFICULT
TO GET IN HORACE MANN
AND BE HIRED AS A BLACK TEACHER.
IF YOU WERE A GOOD
BLACK TEACHER,
IT WAS HARD FOR YOU
TO GET IN THERE.
>> THEY WERE UNDER CONTRACT.
AND EVENTUALLY
THE BUILDINGS DO OPEN AGAIN
AND PUBLIC SCHOOL TEACHERS
GO TO WORK EVERY DAY.
THEY CLOCK IN EVERY DAY.
THEY KEEP THEIR SCHOOL HOURS
EVERY DAY.
narrator: NOW IT'S OCTOBER.
THE SCHOOLS ARE CLOSED.
THE REFERENDUM VOTE
SEALED THE CLOSURES.
AND EVERYONE
IS BEGINNING TO BELIEVE
THE SCHOOLS WILL NOT REOPEN.
THE SCRAMBLE INTENSIFIES
TO FIND AN EDUCATION
FOR THE DISPLACED TEENAGERS
OF LITTLE ROCK.
>> I ENDED UP AT THE CONWAY
COUNTY TRAINING SCHOOL
IN MENIFEE, ARKANSAS,
WHICH IS ABOUT 30 MILES.
IT WAS VERY DIFFICULT
FOR ME TO LEAVE HOME.
I HAD NEVER BEEN AWAY FROM HOME
EXCEPT DURING THE WEEKEND
TO VISIT RELATIVES.
SO THIS WAS AN ENTIRELY
DIFFERENT EXPERIENCE FOR ME.
I MISSED MY PARENTS,
I MISSED MY GRANDPARENT
WHO LIVED WITH US,
MY GRANDFATHER,
AND MY TWO SISTERS.
AND SO THIS WAS REALLY,
REALLY DIFFERENT.
THERE WERE NO OTHER CHILDREN
IN THE HOME THAT I LIVED IN.
>> IF A FAMILY HAD ONE CAR,
THAT WAS THE NORM
AT THIS TIME PERIOD,
AND WITH STAY-AT-HOME MOTHERS
AND PROBABLY
NOT A TWO-PARENT HOUSEHOLD,
HOW COULD A STUDENT
WHO WAS 15 YEARS OLD
GET TO A NEARBY PUBLIC SCHOOL?
>> IT WAS LIKE
SOMETHING OPENED UP,
AND WE ALL FELL IN IT.
KIDS HAD TO GO AWAY
TO RELATIVES' HOMES.
>> I WENT TO LIVE WITH AN AUNT
IN ST. LOUIS
TO CONTINUE MY EDUCATION.
>> OUR VALUES AT THAT TIME
BASICALLY WAS FRIENDSHIPS.
WHEN WE ATTEND SCHOOL,
EVERYBODY WALKED
TO SCHOOL TOGETHER,
WE STUDIED TOGETHER,
WE ATE TOGETHER,
AND YOU PLAYED TOGETHER.
WHEN SCHOOLS CLOSED, OF COURSE,
IT BROKE A LOT OF THE
FRIENDSHIPS AND RELATIONSHIPS
BECAUSE A LOT OF THE STUDENTS
MOVED AWAY.
THERE WERE SOME PARENTS
THAT WAS ABLE
TO GET THEIR KIDS
IN SCHOOLS IN OTHER STATES,
SO YOU DID LOSE A LOT
OF FRIENDS, CLOSE FRIENDS,
DURING THAT PERIOD THAT--
SOME YOU'VE SEEN SINCE
AND SOME YOU'VE NOT.
>> NORTH LITTLE ROCK
MADE THE DECISION IMMEDIATELY
THAT THEY WOULD ACCEPT
NO STUDENT FROM LITTLE ROCK
UNLESS THEY CHANGED RESIDENCE.
>> PEOPLE SET UP BOGUS
RENTAL PLACES IN OTHER CITIES
SO THEIR KIDS
COULD GO TO SCHOOL THERE.
THAT HAPPENED
IN NORTH LITTLE ROCK.
THEY WOULD RENT APARTMENTS OVER
THERE AND USE THOSE ADDRESSES.
>> AND WHEN SCHOOLS DIDN'T OPEN
AND I STARTED THINKING
I'VE GOT TO
COMPLETE HIGH SCHOOL SOMEHOW
IN ORDER TO GO TO COLLEGE.
I WENT DOWN
WITH SOME OF MY FRIENDS.
WE WENT BY
THE MARINE CORPS RECRUITER,
AND HE WASN'T IN.
SO WE STOPPED
AT THE NAVY RECRUITER,
AND HE SAYS, "IF YOU WANT
TO GET AN EDUCATION,
I CAN GET YOU YOUR DIPLOMA."
narrator: PRIVATE SCHOOLS
BEGAN TO OPEN FOR WHITES.
T.J. RANEY HIGH SCHOOL.
>> STUDENTS FOUND
THAT IF THEY WERE GONNA
GO TO SCHOOL IN LITTLE ROCK
AND THEY WERE WHITE,
THEY COULD GO TO RANEY FOR FREE.
MANY OF THEIR FRIENDS
WOULD BE GOING TO RANEY.
THEY WOULD CHOOSE THAT SCHOOL.
>> AND AS FAR AS THE DECISION
TO GO TO RANEY,
IT WAS THERE; IT WAS CHEAP.
THERE WAS NO--
IT WAS LIKE A PUBLIC SCHOOL
ONLY PRIVATE.
I MEAN, THERE WAS NO FUNDS.
IT WASN'T LIKE THE BAPTIST HIGH
WHERE YOU HAD TO PAY TUITION
AND EVERYTHING.
WE WEREN'T POOR BY ANY MEANS,
BUT IT WAS JUST SOMETHING
THAT WAS NOT--
WE COULDN'T AFFORD
A PRIVATE SCHOOL.
>> ABOUT 800-PLUS STUDENTS
ATTENDED RANEY.
THEY DID GRADUATE A CLASS,
AND THEY DID RECEIVE
THEIR ACCREDITATION.
>> WE WAITED,
AND THEN THEY TOLD US
THAT THEY WERE GONNA OPEN
THE PRIVATE SCHOOL.
SO I GOT TO GO
TO THE PRIVATE SCHOOL,
WHICH I TRULY HAD--
I FEEL LIKE I WAS PROBABLY
ONE OF THE LUCKY ONES
BECAUSE I STILL WAS ABLE
TO GO TO SCHOOL
WITH A LOT OF MY FRIENDS
THAT I WENT TO CENTRAL,
AND THEN MY HALL FRIENDS
WERE BROUGHT BACK IN.
AND SO I WAS ABLE TO GRADUATE
WITH SOME OF MY HALL FRIENDS.
>> IF IT HADN'T BEEN
FOR DR. RANEY
AND A FEW OTHER PEOPLE,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I WOULD HAVE
DONE FOR MY SENIOR YEAR.
>> THE SECOND LARGEST
PRIVATE SCHOOL
THAT OPENED FOR WHITES
IN LITTLE ROCK WAS BAPTIST,
AND IT WAS OPERATED
UNDER THE AUSPICES
OF OUACHITA BAPTISTS
AND TWO DOWNTOWN CHURCHES.
THEY USED THE FACILITIES
OF THE SECOND BAPTIST CHURCH.
THEY USED THE YWCA
FOR THEIR P.E. CLASSES.
THEY USED
A BUSINESS SCHOOL DOWNTOWN
FOR THEIR COMMERCIAL CLASSES,
AND THEY HAD
BETWEEN 300 AND 400 STUDENTS.
>> THERE WERE SEVERAL
BOMB SCARES
THAT THE SCHOOL RECEIVED
DURING THE YEAR.
THE BOYS' CLUB WAS ACROSS
THE STREET FROM OUR SCHOOL,
AND WE WOULD GO
ACROSS THE STREET
AND SIT IN THE BOYS' CLUB
WHILE THEY WENT
THROUGH THE SCHOOL
CHECKING FOR ANY BOMBS.
NEVER FOUND ANYTHING,
AS FAR AS I KNOW.
>> MOST OF OUR CLASSES WERE HELD
IN THE EDUCATIONAL BUILDING.
IT WAS A FAIRLY NEW FACILITY,
AND I MEAN, WE WERE
ALL OVER THAT BUILDING,
AS YOU CAN IMAGINE.
>> WHEN YOU CRAMMED 30 DESKS
INTO ONE OF THE CLASSROOMS
IN THE EDUCATIONAL BUILDING,
THEY WERE CRAMMED IN.
THEY WERE VERY CLOSE TOGETHER,
AND WE HAD ABOUT 30 STUDENTS
IN MOST OF OUR CLASSES.
THERE WERE NO WINDOWS
IN THE BUILDING WHATSOEVER.
>> BUT A LOT OF PEOPLE
WERE GOING TO BE IN LITTLE ROCK,
AND THE PARENTS TALKED
AND REALIZED
THAT CORRESPONDENCE COURSES
FROM THE UNIVERSITY
WERE AVAILABLE.
AND THERE WERE TEACHERS WHO
WOULD HELP WITH THOSE CLASSES.
MY CLASSES MET AT PULASKI
HEIGHTS PRESBYTERIAN CHURCH
IN THE AFTERNOON,
AND THERE WERE A LOT OF PEOPLE
THAT I KNEW
THAT WERE TAKING
THE SAME CLASSES.
YOU WERE IN A GROUP.
>> A LOT OF THE SENIORS--
NOT SOPHOMORES AND JUNIORS--
THOUGHT IF THEY COULD
JUST GET AN ENGLISH CREDIT
OR MAYBE ONE MORE MATH CREDIT,
THEN THEY COULD GO ON
TO COLLEGE AT SEMESTER,
AND THIS WAS THE CASE
FOR MANY STUDENTS.
>> I'M ONE OF THESE STUDENTS
BACK THEN
THAT WENT TO ABOUT FIVE OR SIX
DIFFERENT SCHOOLS
IN FIVE OR SIX SUCCESSIVE YEARS.
I STARTED OUT,
WHEN I MOVED HERE,
AT FOREST HEIGHTS JUNIOR HIGH
FOR THE NINTH GRADE
AND THEN WENT TO CENTRAL--
THAT WOULD HAVE BEEN '56, 57,
FOR MY SOPHOMORE YEAR.
THEN I WENT TO HALL
FOR MY JUNIOR YEAR,
WHICH WAS '57, '58.
AND THEN OF COURSE, '58, '59,
THERE WERE NO HIGH SCHOOLS,
SO I WENT AWAY,
AND I FINISHED UP AT ST. STEVENS
IN AUSTIN, TEXAS.
>> MY DADDY TOOK ME
TO LOUISVILLE, ARKANSAS,
TO A COUSIN
THAT I HAD NEVER MET,
HAD NEVER BEEN
TO LOUISVILLE BEFORE,
AND WANTED ME
TO ENROLL IN SCHOOL THERE.
WELL, AFTER BEING THERE
TWO DAYS--
HE STAYED THERE WITH ME
I COULDN'T TAKE IT.
I WENT TO SEE THE SCHOOL,
AND IT'S LIKE,
"NO, I CAN'T DO THIS."
>> AND I WAS ON AN AIRPLANE
GOING TO KANSAS CITY
AND HARDLY REALIZED
WHAT HAD HAPPENED
UNTIL I GOT THERE
AND STARTED SCHOOL.
>> I GUESS PROBABLY THE SECOND,
MAYBE THE THIRD WEEK
IN SEPTEMBER
IS WHEN I ENROLLED IN
PULASKI COUNTY TRAINING SCHOOL.
>> I WOKE UP
ONE SATURDAY MORNING
AND MOTHER AND DADDY CAME IN
AND SAID,
"GENIE, WE THINK WE'RE GONNA
"HAVE TO SEND YOU
AWAY TO SCHOOL.
AND YOU'RE LEAVING TOMORROW."
AND I WAS GOING, "GOODNESS."
AND SO IT WAS,
"TELL EVERYBODY GOOD-BYE."
REALLY, IT WAS A SHOCK.
>> THAT YEAR, I DID NOT GO
TO HIGH SCHOOL.
I STAYED OUT AND I WORKED
FOR THE WHOLE YEAR.
>> WHEN THE SCHOOLS
DID NOT OPEN,
MAYBE FOR THE FIRST WEEK,
MY MOTHER,
WHO WAS A RECENT WIDOW,
WE JUST ASSUMED
THAT THEY WOULD BE OPENING SOON.
SO FOR PROBABLY
ABOUT 2, 2 1/2 WEEKS,
WE SAT AND READ THE PAPER
AND WATCHED TV,
WATCHED THE EVENING NEWS.
AND LITTLE BY LITTLE,
I NOTICED THAT MY FRIENDS
AND CLOSE FRIENDS
WERE GOING AWAY.
THEIR PARENTS
WERE PUTTING THEM IN THE CAR
AND TAKING THEM
TO LIVE WITH RELATIVES,
PUTTING THEM IN COUNTY SCHOOLS.
SO AT THAT TIME,
MY MOTHER DECIDED TO TAKE
MY SISTER AND MYSELF
TO MONTGOMERY, ALABAMA.
>> IT HAPPENED THAT THE DAY
THAT WE SIGNED IN
WAS THE LAST DAY OF THE FIRST
SIX WEEKS OF THEIR SCHOOL.
EVERY CLASS I ATTENDED
TOLD ME THAT I WAS GONNA
HAVE TO TAKE
MY FIRST SIX WEEKS' EXAMS
THE NEXT DAY.
I WAS TAKING ALGEBRA.
I HAD NEVER TAKEN ALGEBRA.
I WAS TAKING LATIN.
I HAD NOT TAKEN LATIN.
I WAS GONNA TAKE
SOME KIND OF ENGLISH EXAM
REGARDING A BOOK THAT
I WAS SUPPOSED TO HAVE READ.
EVERYTHING WAS GOING TO BE
FOREIGN TO ME.
SO MY SISTER AND I
MET AT LUNCHTIME,
DECIDED WE WOULD NOT BE BACK,
AND THE NEXT DAY, WE JUST DIDN'T
GO BACK TO SIDNEY LANIER.
SO AND THE REASON IS,
WE WOULD HAVE BOTH FAILED.
WE KNEW THAT.
WE KNEW THAT THIS WAS NOT
GONNA BE A GOOD SITUATION.
>> SO WE STAYED IN MONTGOMERY,
AGAIN, WATCHING TV,
WATCHING THE EVENING NEWS,
SEEING OUR FRIENDS
TAKING A STAND,
WAITING FOR THE SCHOOLS TO OPEN,
AND FINALLY, WE PACKED IT UP
AND CAME BACK TO LITTLE ROCK.
narrator: HERE ARE SOME
OF THE STATISTICS
OF WHO WENT WHERE THAT YEAR.
>> 44% OF ALL THE WHITE STUDENTS
FOUND PRIVATE SCHOOLING
IN LITTLE ROCK
WHICH WAS A GREAT BONUS
AND BOON FOR THEM.
35% WENT TO OTHER
STATE PUBLIC SCHOOLS.
9% WENT TO PUBLIC
OR PRIVATE SCHOOLS OUT OF STATE.
4% ENTERED COLLEGE EARLY.
AND ALL BUT 7% OF WHITE STUDENTS
FOUND SOME PLACE
TO GO TO SCHOOL.
THAT MIGHT NOT HAVE BEEN
THEIR CHOICE.
IT MIGHT NOT HAVE BEEN
THE EDUCATION
THAT THEY WOULD HAVE RECEIVED
AT CENTRAL HIGH OR HALL HIGH.
BUT THEY WENT SOMEWHERE
TO SCHOOL, ALL BUT 7%.
narrator: BUT THE BLACK CHILDREN
WERE NOT AS FORTUNATE.
ONLY 50% OF THEM
FOUND A SCHOOL TO ATTEND.
>> OF THE PUBLIC SCHOOLS
IN THE STATE, 36%--
THAT'S EVEN MORE THAN WHITES--
WENT TO NEARBY PUBLIC SCHOOLS
OR MOVED IN WITH RELATIVES
OR FOUND A PUBLIC SCHOOL
TO ATTEND.
12% WERE ABLE TO GO TO PUBLIC
OR PRIVATE SCHOOLS OUT OF STATE.
ONLY, I THINK, A TOTAL OF SIX
OF THE BLACK STUDENTS
WERE ABLE
TO ENTER COLLEGE EARLY.
>> I WAS GOING TO BE
IN THE TENTH GRADE,
AND I WAS GOING TO HORACE MANN
HIGH SCHOOL.
AND I ENDED UP GOING
TO J.C. COOK HIGH SCHOOL,
WHICH WAS
IN WRIGHTSVILLE, ARKANSAS.
>> AND I HAD TO GO
TO ST. PETERS IN PINE BLUFF,
WHICH WAS A PRIVATE
CATHOLIC SCHOOL.
>> DURING THAT TIME SPAN
THAT THE SCHOOLS WERE CLOSED,
IT WAS VERY,
VERY HEARTBREAKING TO ME,
BECAUSE I HAD AN ASPIRATION
OF BECOMING AN ATTORNEY.
I REALLY WANTED TO GO INTO LAW.
THE BEST THAT I COULD DO
WAS TO WORK WHEN I COULD,
AND BEING A YOUNG CHILD,
OBVIOUSLY THERE'S VERY LITTLE
WORK YOU CAN DO
OTHER THAN TO CUT YARDS.
>> 50% OF BLACK STUDENTS
FOUND NO SCHOOLING
BECAUSE NO PRIVATE EDUCATION
FOR BLACKS
EMERGED IN LITTLE ROCK.
narrator:
A QUOTE FROM ROY WILKINS,
EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR OF THE NAACP,
EXPLAINS WHY.
>> "THE SEGREGATIONISTS
"HAVE SET UP
THEIR TEMPORARY SCHOOLS
"TO DEFY THE LAW.
"IF WE JOIN THEM
AND SET UP OUR SCHOOLS,
"WE WILL BE
DEFYING THE LAW ALSO.
"BESIDES, WE WOULD BE DOING
JUST WHAT THEY WANT US TO DO.
"IN ADDITION, WE WOULD BE
SELLING OUT THE YOUNGSTERS
"WHO ENDURED THE PERSECUTION
AT CENTRAL HIGH LAST YEAR.
"WE WOULD BE BETRAYING
ALL OTHER NEGRO CHILDREN
"THROUGHOUT THE NATION
WHO HOPE TO GO FORWARD
TO FULL OPPORTUNITY."
narrator: WHAT WERE
THE STUDENTS THEMSELVES
THINKING ABOUT
THE CLOSED SCHOOLS?
DID THEY HAVE THE SAME STRONG
OPPOSITION TO INTEGRATION
AS DID THEIR PARENTS'
GENERATION?
>> I WAS NEVER INVOLVED
IN ANY OF THE ACTIVITIES
THAT I THOUGHT
WERE NEGATIVE SITUATIONS
WITH SOME OF THE BLACK PEOPLE
THAT HAD COME TO CENTRAL.
THEY WEREN'T
IN ANY OF MY CLASSES, WHICH--
IT JUST HAPPENED THAT WAY.
IT WASN'T, YOU KNOW, BY CHOICE.
AND I, FRANKLY, DIDN'T MIND
THAT THEY WERE THERE.
I THOUGHT WE COULD--
IT WAS A HUGE SCHOOL.
WE HAD LOTS OF STUDENTS.
YOU KNOW, A FEW MORE,
IT DIDN'T MATTER.
I DIDN'T THINK
IT WOULD INTERFERE
WITH OUR EDUCATION AT ALL.
AND IT WAS OKAY WITH ME.
>> IN SEPTEMBER OF 1958,
WHEN THE SCHOOLS
HAD REMAINED CLOSED
AND HAD NOT YET BEEN OPEN,
THE STUDENTS THEMSELVES
TOOK IT UPON THEMSELVES
TO MAIL OUT POSTCARDS.
AND STUDENTS AT CENTRAL
AND AT HALL
MAILED OUT POSTCARDS ASKING THEM
HOW THEY FAVORED
OPENING THE SCHOOLS
EVEN WITH INTEGRATION.
AND 71% OF THE STUDENTS AT HALL
SAID YES.
AND THE VOTE WAS ALSO FAVORABLE
AT CENTRAL.
THIS TELLS US THAT 18-YEAR-OLDS
COULDN'T VOTE IN THE 1950s.
SO THERE--PERHAPS OUR STUDENTS,
OUR CHILDREN
WERE MORE ENLIGHTENED
THAN THEIR PARENTS.
PERHAPS THEY REPRESENTED
A NEW THOUGHT,
A NEW WAY OF THINKING.
>> I WAS MAD BACK THEN.
I WAS MAD MAINLY AT THE PARENTS
AND THE STUDENTS
WHO WERE RECEIVING
ALL OF THE ATTENTION
AND MADE THE REST OF US SUFFER.
>> I NEVER WORRIED
ABOUT INTEGRATION.
AND I THINK
THAT IF THEY HAD OFFERED--
ESPECIALLY THE SENIORS
THE OPPORTUNITY TO VOTE,
IT WOULD HAVE
BEEN OVERWHELMINGLY
IN FAVOR OF OPENING THE SCHOOLS.
INTEGRATION WAS
NOT REALLY A PROBLEM
WITH THE GREATEST MAJORITY
OF THEM.
I'VE SAID MANY, MANY TIMES
THAT IF THEY HAD EXPELLED
ABOUT TWO DOZEN KIDS,
THEY PROBABLY WOULDN'T HAVE
NEEDED THE NATIONAL GUARD THERE.
>> YOU LIKE TO THINK
THAT THOSE WERE THE AGITATORS.
BECAUSE I CERTAINLY DON'T THINK
THOSE WERE THE MAINSTREAM
STUDENTS AT CENTRAL.
THOSE WERE NOT THE LEADERS.
THOSE WERE NOT THE REALLY NORMAL
GOOD KIDS
WHO WENT TO HIGH SCHOOL.
narrator: BUT THE 1958, '59
SCHOOL YEAR WAS TICKING AWAY,
AND MANY STUDENTS STILL HADN'T
FOUND A SCHOOL TO ATTEND.
>> I WAS GOING TO LITTLE ROCK
CENTRAL HIGH SCHOOL
AND WOULD HAVE BEEN A SENIOR
THE NEXT--IN THE '58 FALL,
AND THAT DIDN'T HAPPEN.
AND WE JUST SAT AND WAITED
AND WAITED AND WAITED.
SO THE FIRST OF OCTOBER,
I WENT TO DE QUEEN.
>> YOU CAN IMAGINE PARENTS
ON THE PHONE,
STUDENTS ON THE PHONE,
"I WANT TO GO
WHERE MY FRIEND IS GOING."
THEY DROVE TO JACKSONVILLE.
THEY HAD CARPOOLS TO MAPLEVILLE.
THEY HAD CARPOOLS
TO NEARBY SCHOOLS
SO THAT THOSE STUDENTS
COULD STAY AT HOME,
BUT EVENTUALLY THEY REACHED
THEIR TOTAL ENROLLMENT
AND COULD NOT
TAKE ANY MORE STUDENTS.
THE LONGER YOU WAITED,
THE MORE--
THE GREATER THE DISTANCE
YOU HAD TO GO TO FIND A SCHOOL.
>> WELL, WE HARDLY HAD A CHANCE
TO SAY GOOD-BYE.
BECAUSE I THINK EVERYBODY
WAS MAKING PLANS
AND HAD TO DO THEM RATHER
QUICKLY WITHOUT ANY PREPLANNING.
IT WAS KIND OF LIKE,
"OKAY, WE'RE IN A CRISIS.
"WHAT SHOULD WE DO?
HOW CAN WE GET THROUGH THIS?"
>> MOST OF THE STUDENTS
WHO DID MOVE IN WITH RELATIVES
DID NOT MAKE THAT MOVE
UNTIL, SAY, OCTOBER,
AS LATE AS OCTOBER.
SOME DID NOT EVEN GO
THE WHOLE FIRST SEMESTER,
BUT BY SEMESTER, MANY PARENTS
HAD MADE THE DECISION
THAT IT WAS BETTER
TO SEND THEIR 15-YEAR-OLD CHILD
OFF TO A RESIDENTIAL HIGH SCHOOL
THAN TO LET THEM
NOT GO TO SCHOOL AT ALL.
>> SECOND SEMESTER STARTED.
I WENT TO HARDING ACADEMY,
WHICH IS A CHURCH OF CHRIST
BOARDING SCHOOL.
IT WAS A VERY INTERESTING
EXPERIENCE FOR ME
AND A VERY EYE-OPENING
BECAUSE I'M JEWISH,
AND IT IS CHURCH OF CHRIST.
narrator: THE SEGREGATIONISTS
WERE WELL-ORGANIZED
WITH THE CAPITAL CITIZENS'
COUNCIL
AND THE CENTRAL HIGH
MOTHERS' LEAGUE.
>> SOME GROUPS ALREADY EXISTED
THAT WERE LEFT OVER
FROM EARLIER--FROM THE BEGINNING
OF INTEGRATION
OR COURT-IMPLEMENTED
INTEGRATION.
THE CAPITAL CITIZENS' COUNCIL
WAS A WHITE CITIZENS' COUNCIL
THAT WAS AN IMPORTANT FACTOR
IN ALL OF THIS IN LITTLE ROCK.
AND THEY HAD HELPED
ENCOURAGE PEOPLE
TO COME OUT AROUND CENTRAL HIGH
AND PROTEST.
>> THAT'S ONE OF THE THINGS THAT
HAPPENED BETWEEN '54 AND '57
IS THE ORGANIZATION OF THESE
WHITE CITIZEN COUNCILS.
AND WHILE THEY REPRESENT,
MEMBERSHIP-WISE,
A SMALL PERCENTAGE
OF POPULATION,
THEY GET THE ATTENTION
IN THE PRESS
THAT CAUSES LOTS OF ATTENTION
TO GO OUT.
AND COMMON ORDINARY FOLK
WHO ARE NOT GOING
TO JOIN THE COUNCIL
BUT SEE THIS
AS GIVING VOICE TO MAYBE
THEIR DEEPEST INNER FEELINGS
ALONG THE WAY.
>> WE GOT THE WORD
FROM SOME OF THE WHITE CITIZENS'
COUNCIL PEOPLE
THAT THEY WERE BRINGING A LOAD.
THEY WERE COMING IN.
THEY WERE GONNA STOP IT
ONE WAY OR THE OTHER.
AND GOVERNOR FAUBUS
WAS FACED WITH THAT PROSPECT
OF HAVING PEOPLE HURT OR KILLED.
HE DIDN'T WANT THAT.
I DON'T THINK HE WOULD HAVE EVER
CLOSED THE SCHOOLS
IF HE'D THOUGHT
IT COULD BE PEACEFUL.
>> WAS THERE REALLY
GOING TO BE RIOTING
AND KNIFINGS AND KILLINGS AND--
WAS THAT REALLY GOING TO OCCUR?
AND WE FOUND IT HARD TO BELIEVE
THAT THERE WAS A THREAT
SO STRONG.
>> ANOTHER GROUP
OF WHITE SEGREGATIONISTS
WAS THE MOTHERS' LEAGUE
OF CENTRAL HIGH.
THEY CLAIMED TO BE A GROUP
THAT WANTED TO PREVENT
INTEGRATION AT CENTRAL.
SO THEY HAD BEEN AROUND
AND HAD BEEN IN EXISTENCE
SINCE 1957.
THESE GROUPS ARE WORKING
IN EVERY WAY POSSIBLE.
THEY ARE PUTTING OUT THE WORD.
THEY ARE GETTING PRESS.
THEY ARE MAKING TELEPHONE CALLS.
THEY ARE DOING THEIR WORK
TO INFLUENCE ANY ELECTION
THAT WOULD OCCUR
IN THE LOST YEAR IN LITTLE ROCK.
YOU WILL HEAR ME SAY
SEGREGATIONIST,
BUT YOU NEVER HEAR ME SAY
INTEGRATIONIST.
AND THAT IS BECAUSE THERE WERE
SO FEW TRUE INTEGRATIONISTS.
THERE WERE PEOPLE IN THE
COMMUNITY WHO WERE MODERATES
WHO WERE WILLING TO ACCEPT
TOKEN INTEGRATION
AND FOLLOW THE LETTER OF THE LAW
AND TO FOLLOW
THE COURT DIRECTIVE
AND TO GRADUALLY MOVE TOWARD
INTEGRATION OF THE RACES,
BUT WHOLESALE INTEGRATION
WAS NOT TO COME IN THE SOUTH
IN ARKANSAS, IN LITTLE ROCK,
UNTIL BUSING IN THE 1970s.
SO WE'RE BACK IN THE 1950s,
AND TO EVEN MAKE TOKEN
INTEGRATION OF THE PUBLIC SCHOOL
WAS AN ENORMOUS CHANGE.
narrator: THE ONE LONE,
STRONG, AND COURAGEOUS VOICE
OF THE MODERATES EMERGED
AS THE WOMEN'S EMERGENCY
COMMITTEE TO OPEN OUR SCHOOLS.
THESE WERE WHITE WOMEN
WHO BEGAN
WORKING ON THE NEW CRISIS
AT THE BEGINNING
OF THE SCHOOL YEAR.
>> I JUST DID A TALK ON
ADOLPHINE FLETCHER TERRY.
SHE CALLED OUT THE WOMEN
AFTER TELLING, I THINK,
HARRY ASHMORE,
WHO WAS THE EDITOR
OF THE EDITORIAL PAGE
AT THEARKANSAS GAZETTETHAT,
"THE MEN HAVE FAILED US AGAIN.
IT'S TIME
TO CALL OUT THE LADIES."
AND THAT WAS THE INCEPTION
OF THE WOMEN'S
EMERGENCY COMMITTEE
TO OPEN THE SCHOOLS,
WHICH THEY DID.
>> WENT TO THE MEETING
THAT WAS BEING CALLED
OVER AT MRS. TERRY'S,
AND I WAS IMMEDIATELY
PUT TO WORK
SIMPLY BECAUSE I WAS THE ONLY
YOUNG ONE THERE.
AND I WAS FORTUNATE ENOUGH
TO HAVE A SITTER
BECAUSE I HAD
ALL THESE CHILDREN--
AT THAT TIME, I ONLY HAD FOUR,
BUT I HAD DECIDED THAT
I'D DRIVE A CAR FOR 13 YEARS
IF I COULD HAVE SOMEBODY
WHO WOULD BABY-SIT
AND SO THAT I COULD CONTINUE
WITH MY ACTIVITIES.
I DIDN'T WORK, BUT--
AND IT WAS JUST, LIKE,
A HALF A DAY THING,
BUT STILL.
THEY DIDN'T REALLY HAVE
ANY OFFICERS AT THAT TIME,
BUT IT WAS--
BE IN PUBLIC RELATIONS.
>> THEY FORMED A GROUP
WITH THE INTENTION
OF OPENING THE PUBLIC SCHOOLS.
AND THEY ACTUALLY TRIED TO,
IN THEIR PUBLICITY,
DISTANCE THEMSELVES
FROM THE IDEA
OF EITHER INTEGRATION
OR SEGREGATION AND SIMPLY SAY,
"WE ARE WOMEN WHO ARE TRYING
TO OPEN THE PUBLIC SCHOOL SYSTEM
FOR EVERYONE."
>> I WAS JUST REALLY,
REALLY SURPRISED
AND PARTICULARLY SURPRISED
AT THE CHURCH PEOPLE
WHO HAD HAD THE SAME KIND
OF TEACHINGS THAT I HAD HAD
AND HOW THEY COULD BE
SO HYPOCRITICAL
AS TO HAVE, ALL THOSE YEARS,
ACTED AS IF
THEY BELIEVED THOSE THINGS,
AND THEY HAD NOT EVER EXPRESSED
"EVERYBODY BUT."
>> THERE WAS NO OTHER
PUBLIC VOICE
EXCEPT THESE
VERY COURAGEOUS WOMEN.
>> BY THIS TIME, OF COURSE,
I'D READ ENOUGH,
AND I KNEW ABOUT HATRED,
BUT IT DIDN'T--
I THOUGHT THOSE
WERE THE UGLY PEOPLE.
>> THERE WAS A MODEL BY THE TIME
OF THE LOST YEAR
THAT YOUNG, OLD,
WHATEVER, BUSINESSMEN
DID NOT SPEAK OUT.
NOW, THAT IS NOT TO SAY
THAT IN THEIR PERSONAL HOMES
THEY DID NOT
ENCOURAGE THEIR WIVES
TO JOIN
THE WOMEN'S EMERGENCY COMMITTEE
OR TO WORK BEHIND THE SCENES.
PUT YOURSELF IN THE SEAT
OF A SCHOOL BOARD MEMBER.
THE FEDERAL COURTS HAVE TOLD YOU
THAT YOU MUST
INTEGRATE YOUR SCHOOL
AND FOLLOW WITH THE INTEGRATION
PLAN THAT YOU HAVE OUTLINED.
THE STATE AND YOUR GOVERNOR
ARE TELLING YOU THAT YOU CANNOT,
AND THEY HAVE INTERVENED
BY PASSING A LAW
TO CLOSE THE VERY SCHOOLS
THAT YOU HAVE AGREED
TO INTEGRATE
AND TO CLOSE
ALL OTHER HIGH SCHOOLS.
THEY WERE FRUSTRATED,
THEY WERE TARGETED BY PEOPLE
WHO DID NOT APPROVE
OF WHAT THEY HAD TRIED TO DO,
AND THEY WERE--ONE OF THEM
HAS A QUOTE THAT SAID,
"IT WAS A HELPLESS
AND HOPELESS SITUATION.
"WE HAVE NO ALTERNATIVE.
OUR HANDS ARE TIED."
AND SO THE ENTIRE SCHOOL BOARD
RESIGNED.
narrator: ANOTHER INTERESTING
EVENT OCCURRED ABOUT THIS TIME.
A POPULAR MODERATE CONGRESSMAN,
BROOKS HAYS,
WAS UNSEATED BY ONE
OF THE REIGNING SEGREGATIONISTS
ON THE SCHOOL BOARD,
DR. DALE ALFORD.
>> BROOKS HAYS
IS A GOOD EXAMPLE,
I THINK, OF AN INDIVIDUAL
WHO DID STAND ABOVE THE NORM
AND BE ABLE TO SPEAK
TO OUR BEST INTEREST.
BUT HE ALSO WAS DEFEATED.
AND, YOU KNOW, HE COMMITTED
POLITICAL SUICIDE IN DOING THAT.
>> SO THERE HAD TO BE
AN ELECTION IN DECEMBER
OF A COMPLETELY NEW
SCHOOL BOARD.
ONE HAD GONE TO CONGRESS,
AND THE OTHERS HAD RESIGNED.
AND SO THIS IS A CHANCE
FOR THE PARENTS
AND THE POWERS THAT BE,
THE SEGREGATIONIST GROUPS
AND THE MORE MODERATE GROUPS,
TO PUT THEIR POWER
INTO AN ELECTION.
narrator:
AND AFTER A STRONG FIGHT
BY BOTH THE SEGREGATIONISTS
AND THE MODERATES,
THE NEW SCHOOL BOARD
WAS ELECTED.
IT WAS A THREE TO THREE SPLIT:
THREE MODERATES,
THREE SEGREGATIONISTS.
MEANWHILE, WHAT WAS HAPPENING
TO ALL THESE EDUCATORS
UNDER CONTRACT
TO THE PUBLIC SCHOOL SYSTEM?
>> THERE WERE 177 TEACHERS
AND ADMINISTRATORS
WHO WERE LOCKED IN
TO THEIR BUILDINGS.
>> SOME OF THE TEACHERS
WOULD TELL US
IN THE ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
AND JUNIOR HIGH,
"Y'ALL OVER THERE
ARE DOING NOTHING."
BUT WE WERE NOT.
WITH THE CLASSES
WAS FORMED AT FIRST,
AND SO WE WENT TO CLASSES.
LATER ON WHEN WE FOUND OUT THAT,
I GUESS, THE SCHOOL DISTRICT
DECIDED THEY WERE LOSING MONEY
BY PAYING US TO NOT HAVE
STUDENTS IN OUR CLASSES.
THEY DECIDED THEY WOULD USE US
AS SUBSTITUTES,
AND THE SUBSTITUTES CAME LATER.
THEY DIDN'T COME
IN THE FIRST OF THE YEAR.
>> SO THE RULE BECAME
THAT IN THE MORNINGS,
THEY WOULD WORK
IN THEIR CLASSROOMS
PREPARING MATERIALS,
ENRICHING THEMSELVES
IN SOME WAY, SHAPE, OR FORM
TO BE BETTER TEACHERS.
AND IN THE AFTERNOON,
BEGINNING AT NOON,
THEY WOULD HAVE CLASSES
THAT THEY TAUGHT EACH OTHER.
BEFORE LONG,
THE SCHOOL BOARD REALIZED
THAT THE AMOUNT OF MONEY THAT
WAS BEING PAID TO THESE TEACHERS
WAS PRETTY MUCH A LOSS TO THEM,
ESPECIALLY WHEN THE MONEY
HAD TO FOLLOW THE STUDENT
TO ANOTHER PUBLIC SCHOOL.
SO THEY IMMEDIATELY DECIDED,
ABOUT NOVEMBER,
THAT ALL PUBLIC SCHOOL TEACHERS
WOULD NO LONGER
HAVE REGULAR SUBSTITUTES
WHO HAD TO BE PAID.
BUT TEACHERS
FROM THE HIGH SCHOOLS
WOULD GO OUT AND BE SUBSTITUTES.
>> I WAS NOT TOO PLEASED,
REALLY,
TO TEACH IN THE ELEMENTARY
SCHOOL NOR JUNIOR HIGH
BECAUSE THAT WAS NOT MY CALLING,
I FELT LIKE IT.
BUT I DID A GOOD JOB
WHEN I WENT,
HOPING I WOULDN'T HAVE TO
GO AGAIN.
>> HOW DID THEY FEEL
ABOUT CLOSED SCHOOLS?
THEY WERE VERY FRUSTRATED.
THEY SAID THINGS LIKE,
"WE WERE LIKE FISH OUT OF WATER.
WE PREPARED AND PREPARED."
AND AS THE STUDENTS AND AS
THE PARENTS IN THE COMMUNITY,
THEY WERE HOPEFUL.
narrator: IN JANUARY, THE NEW
YEAR BROUGHT SOME SMALL CHANGES
BY ONE MALE LEADER SPEAKING OUT
FOR PUBLIC EDUCATION.
>> THE NEW PRESIDENCY
OF GRAINGER WILLIAMS
AT THE CHAMBER OF COMMERCE
AND UNDER HIS LEADERSHIP,
THEY DO MAKE A PUBLIC STATEMENT
ENCOURAGING THE OPENING
OF THE SCHOOL.
narrator: BUT THE GENERAL
ASSEMBLY IS BACK IN SESSION.
AND FAUBUS AND HIS FOLLOWERS
ARE PREPARING
TO PASS MORE BILLS
TO BLOCK INTEGRATION.
>> THERE WAS AN ATTEMPT
BY SOME OF FAUBUS' COMPATRIOTS
TO PASS WHAT WAS CALLED
A BOARD PACKING BILL.
THE SCHOOL BOARD IS SPLIT
AFTER DECEMBER
WITH THREE SEGREGATIONISTS
AND THREE MODERATES.
AND IF THEY COULD PASS A LAW
THAT WOULD ALLOW
SCHOOL BOARD MEMBERS
TO EXIST WITH MORE
THAN SIX PEOPLE,
THEN THEY, PERHAPS, COULD GET
AN APPOINTED MEMBER
OR AN ELECTED
SEGREGATIONIST THERE
TO TURN THE TIDE
ON THE BOARD PACKING BILL.
THIS FAILED.
IN ELIZABETH HUCKABEE'S DIARY,
WHICH WAS SO IMPORTANT
TO MY UNDERSTANDING
OF THE INSIDE STORY
OF THE LOST YEAR,
SHE DOCUMENTED EVERYTHING,
AND SHE SAID WHEN
THE BOARD PACKING BILL FAILED,
SHE SAID, "WE ARE SAVED.
SENATOR FAGAN HAS SAVED US."
AND SO THIS BILL WAS DEFEATED.
>> MY FATHER WAS
IN SUPPORT OF EDUCATION,
AND HE WAS TRYING, I THINK,
VERY HARD TO AVOID
TAKING A STAND ON INTEGRATION
OR SEGREGATION BUT WANTED
TO KEEP THE SCHOOLS OPEN.
HE DIDN'T FEEL LIKE
THAT THAT POLITICAL BATTLE
WAS TO BE HELD IN THE CLASSROOM.
SO I DON'T THINK STUDENTS
WERE AS TRAUMATIZED
BY THE FACT
THAT WE WERE GONNA INTEGRATE
OR DID INTEGRATE
THE YEAR BEFORE.
I THINK THE ADULTS WERE THE ONES
THAT WERE RIDDLED WITH FEAR.
WE WERE JUST TEENAGERS
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO FIT IN ALL OF THE CHANGES
THAT WERE TAKING PLACE
AROUND US.
BUT OUR FAMILY,
BECAUSE OF MY FATHER'S POSITION
AND THE POWER
THAT HE HELD IN THE SENATE
AND HAD FOR A NUMBER OF YEARS,
WE TOOK A BEATING OVER IT.
PEOPLE REALLY
LASHED OUT PERSONALLY,
MADE PERSONAL ATTACKS
ON OUR FAMILY.
AND EVEN FRIENDS
WERE AFRAID TO BE AROUND US
OR TO RIDE TO SCHOOL WITH ME
AT THAT TIME AT SYLVAN HILLS
BECAUSE THEY WEREN'T CERTAIN
THAT THE CAR
WOULDN'T BE RUN OFF THE ROAD.
>> WHAT THE LOST YEAR DOES IS,
IT SPLITS THE WHITE COMMUNITY.
IT SPLITS IT,
AND IT MAKES THAT DIVISION
IN THE WHITE COMMUNITY DEEPER
AND WIDER AND MORE COMBATIVE.
narrator: IN MAY OF 1959,
AN EVENT HAPPENED
THAT WOULD CHANGE THE ATMOSPHERE
IN LITTLE ROCK.
THE SCHOOL BOARD
WENT INTO SESSION
TO REVIEW TEACHER'S CONTRACTS
FOR THE COMING YEAR.
WITHOUT A QUORUM,
THE SEGREGATIONISTS
PROCEEDED TO FIRE 44 TEACHERS
AND ADMINISTRATORS.
>> THE IDEA OF A PURGE
HAS BEEN CIRCULATING,
AND EVERYONE'S FEELING
A LITTLE UNEASY ABOUT THIS.
EVERY ISSUE
THAT CAME BEFORE THE BOARD
AS HAD BEEN IN RECENT MONTHS,
ENDED WITH A THREE-THREE VOTE.
THEY WERE ABSOLUTELY SPLIT.
SO WHEN THEY BROKE FOR LUNCH,
WITH RECOMMENDATIONS
BY LEGAL COUNSEL,
THE MODERATE MEMBERS
OF THE SCHOOL BOARD
DECIDED TO LEAVE, SIMPLY
TO NOT COME BACK AFTER LUNCH.
AND THEY THOUGHT BY DOING THIS
THERE WOULD BE NO QUORUM
IN THE SIX MEMBER BOARD.
AND THEREFORE,
THEY COULD NOT DO THEIR INTENT
OF TRYING TO PURGE TEACHERS.
THEY FIRE 44 TEACHERS
AND ADMINISTRATORS.
MOST ARE WHITE;
A FEW ARE BLACK.
MOST OF THEM
WERE FROM CENTRAL HIGH,
BUT NOT ALL WERE.
SOME WERE
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL PRINCIPALS,
EVEN TWO SECRETARIES.
>> I WAS IN THE CARPOOL.
I THINK WE HAD THE RADIO ON,
AND WITH THREE OTHER TEACHERS,
AND WE HEARD THAT THREE PEOPLE
HAD MET AND FIRED US.
AND THEN WE RECEIVED A LETTER.
>> "THIS IS TO NOTIFY YOU
THAT YOUR CONTRACT
"WITH THE LITTLE ROCK
SCHOOL DISTRICT
HAS NOT
AND WILL NOT BE RENEWED."
>> I COULD THINK OF TWO REASONS
THAT I WOULD BE.
ONE WOULD HAVE BEEN MY INTERVIEW
WITH THE STATE POLICE,
AND THEN THE OTHER WAS THAT
I WOULD NOT SIGN MY CONTRACT,
A CONTRACT
WITH A PRIVATE SCHOOL.
>> MOST OF THEM
BELIEVE THAT THEY WERE LABELED
AS THE COOPERATIONISTS,
THOSE PEOPLE WHO HAVE
COOPERATED WITH OR ENDORSED
OR WERE SYMPATHETIC
TO THE LITTLE ROCK NINE
AND TO THE INTEGRATION
OF THE SCHOOLS.
narrator:
THE PURGE OF THE TEACHERS
BY THE SEGREGATIONISTS
GAVE THE MODERATES A WAY
TO RALLY ALL THEIR SUPPORTERS.
>> HOW CAN WE GET SCHOOLS OPEN
WITHOUT SAYING WE'RE ABSOLUTELY
FOR INTEGRATION?
>> BECAUSE YOU WERE ALWAYS
TRYING TO MAKE THIS
NOT AN INTEGRATION-SEGREGATION
DECISION
BUT INSTEAD A REOPENING
OF THE PUBLIC SCHOOLS.
>> IF YOU PURGE OUR REVERED
AND RESPECTED TEACHERS,
YOU HAVE OVERSTEPPED.
YOU'VE TAKEN AWAY
THEIR DUE PROCESS.
YOU'VE COMPLETELY
BROKEN THE LAW.
AND SO THIS GIVES THEM
A RALLYING CRY.
SO WITHIN DAYS AFTER THE PURGE,
THE WOMEN'S EMERGENCY COMMITTEE,
OF COURSE,
CONVENES IMMEDIATELY.
THEY MAKE
THE FIRST PUBLIC STATEMENT
ENDORSING THE TEACHERS
WHO'VE BEEN PURGED.
narrator: FINALLY,
AS THE COMMUNITY ATTITUDE
IS BEGINNING TO SHIFT,
THE STOP COMMITTEE IS FORMED.
BOTH ADULTS AND LOST YEAR TEENS
PICKED UP THE BANNER
OF THE STOP CAMPAIGN.
AND THE TIDE BEGAN TO TURN
IN LITTLE ROCK.
>> STOP STOOD FOR
STOP THIS OUTRAGEOUS PURGE.
AND IT BECAME SOMETHING OTHER
THAN THE W.E.C.
IT BECAME A FOCUS
ON THE FIRING OF THE TEACHERS,
AND THEY BEGAN
A 20-DAY CAMPAIGN.
WHAT COULD THEY DO?
THEY COULD USE THE NEW LAW
THAT ALLOWED FOR THE RECALL
OF A BOARD MEMBER.
THEY CAN USE IT
AGAINST THE SEGREGATIONISTS.
SO THEY HAVE
TO GET THE PETITIONS.
THEY HAVE
TO GET THE PETITIONS SIGNED.
THEY SET UP PLACES TO SIGN
AT WAR MEMORIAL STADIUM,
HAD PEOPLE DRIVE DOWN THERE
AND SIGN THE PETITION.
THEY PUSHED THEIR ADVERTISING.
THEY WENT DOOR TO DOOR.
THEY HAD BEEN ORGANIZED
FOR A YEAR,
KNOWING THE VOTERS
IN EACH PRECINCT.
THEY KICKED INTO ACTION.
OFTENTIMES STOP
GETS THE CREDIT FOR THIS,
BUT THE WOMEN'S
EMERGENCY COMMITTEE
WERE DOING THE WORK
BEHIND THE SCENES.
>> I THINK IRVING SPITZBERG
AND I WERE CO-CHAIRMEN
OF THE JUNIOR STOP COMMITTEE,
WHICH TRIED TO ORGANIZE
HIGH SCHOOL STUDENTS
TO HELP WITH THE STOP CAMPAIGN.
narrator: OF COURSE,
THERE WAS OPPOSITION TO THIS,
AND THE SEGREGATIONISTS
FORMED CROSS:
COMMITTEE TO RETAIN
OUR SEGREGATED SCHOOLS.
>> THE MOTHERS' LEAGUE
OF CENTRAL HIGH,
THE CAPITAL CITIZENS' COUNCIL,
THE SEGREGATIONISTS
RALLIED TO THE CROSS CAMPAIGN.
THE OUTCOME OF THE VOTE
ON MAY 25TH
WAS A NARROW--
A VERY NARROW VICTORY
FOR THE MODERATES,
BECAUSE THEY WERE SUCCESSFUL
IN RECALLING
THE MORE SEGREGATIONIST SCHOOL
BOARD MEMBERS.
>> THE BLACK COMMUNITY
AND THE SILK STOCKING DISTRICTS
WON THE ELECTION.
AND IT WAS DONE
BECAUSE OF THE SOPHISTICATION
OF THE WOMEN'S
EMERGENCY COMMITTEE
AND HENRY WOODS AND THE ABILITY
TO DO THIS TARGETING.
AND THE FACT
THAT WE COULD DO THE--
HAD ALL THESE PILES OF CARDS,
AND IT WAS
A SOPHISTICATED CAMPAIGN,
AND WE TURNED OUT THE VOTE.
ONE OF THE THINGS TO UNDERSTAND
ABOUT WHAT WAS
A NECESSARY CONDITION
FOR HAVING
THE REOPENING OF THE SCHOOLS
THROUGH THE STOP CAMPAIGN
WAS THE FACT
THAT ALL OF THE FAMILIES
OF EVERYBODY INVOLVED
HAD BEEN PART
OF THE PUBLIC SCHOOL SYSTEM.
AND IN LITTLE ROCK,
IN BOTH THE BLACK COMMUNITY
AND THE WHITE COMMUNITY,
THERE WAS A SENSE OF GREAT PRIDE
IN THE SCHOOL SYSTEM.
AND TODAY IN MOST OF THE MAJOR
CITIES IN THE UNITED STATES,
ONE WOULD NOT HAVE
THE SAME SORT OF RESPONSE
FROM THE BURGER ELITE
TO ANY ATTACK
ON THE SCHOOL SYSTEM
BECAUSE THEY SIMPLY
AREN'T ENROLLED IN IT.
AND THIS IS
ONE OF THE GREAT WORRIES
ABOUT HOW COMMUNITIES
IN THE UNITED STATES--
AND THIS IS NOT
JUST LITTLE ROCK--
COMMUNITIES
IN THE UNITED STATES
WILL RESPOND TO CRISES
IN THEIR COMMUNITIES
IF ALL OF THE PARTS
OF THE COMMUNITY
AREN'T ENROLLED IN
THE MAJOR PUBLIC INSTITUTIONS
OF THE LARGER SOCIETY.
AND SO THAT WHEN YOU HAVE
WHAT YOU HAVE
IN LITTLE ROCK TODAY,
ALL THESE PRIVATE SCHOOLS,
WHERE MOST OF THE UPPER
MIDDLE CLASS SEND THEIR KIDS,
YOU LOSE WHAT I CALL
THE MORAL CRUNCH
OF THE EXPERIENCE
OF MAKING DECISIONS
ABOUT THE LIFE OF THE COMMUNITY.
BECAUSE IF YOUR PERSONAL
INTERESTS AREN'T AT STAKE,
IF YOU DO NOT HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT YOU YOURSELF
OR YOUR FAMILY
BEING AFFECTED BY DECISIONS,
THEN IT'S VERY DIFFICULT
TO GET ETHICAL DECISIONS.
AND IT'S VERY DIFFICULT
TO GET RATIONAL DECISIONS.
BECAUSE IF YOU'RE NOT
GONNA HAVE--
IF THE DECISIONS
AREN'T REALLY GONNA IMPACT YOU,
YOUR ATTENTION
TO WHAT'S INVOLVED
IS SEVERELY COMPROMISED.
AND SO IF ONE HAD
THE LITTLE ROCK CRISIS TODAY,
IF ONE HAD THE GOVERNOR
SAY THAT HE WAS
GOING TO SHUT DOWN
THE LITTLE ROCK PUBLIC SCHOOLS,
I'M AFRAID THAT SO MANY PEOPLE
WOULD RESPOND THIS WAY.
[yawns]
"OH, WHAT A SHAME."
AND THAT WOULD BE
A TERRIBLE SHAME INDEED.
narrator: ALTHOUGH MANY FAMILIES
IN LITTLE ROCK
DIDN'T THINK THE SCHOOLS WOULD
REOPEN THAT FOLLOWING YEAR
AND MADE PLANS FOR THEIR TEENS
TO GO ELSEWHERE--
>> WE HAD THESE JUNIORS WHO,
IF YOU'RE NOT GONNA GET THIS
STARTED THIS YEAR,
WELL, YOU'RE NOT GONNA HAVE IT
STARTED NEXT YEAR.
SO THERE'S NO POINT
IN US HANGING AROUND
WAITING TO SEE
WHAT WE'RE NOT GONNA DO.
narrator: THE FOUR HIGH SCHOOLS
DID REOPEN IN AUGUST OF 1959
BUT NOT WITHOUT CONFLICT.
THREE BOMBS
WERE EXPLODED IN THE CITY
AT THE OPENING
OF THAT SCHOOL YEAR.
>> THE FIRST DAY OF SCHOOL,
THERE WAS A RALLY
OUTSIDE THE STATE CAPITOL,
AND THE MARCHERS MARCHED
WITH SIGNS
AND CONFEDERATE FLAGS IN CARS
TO CENTRAL HIGH.
IT'S NOT THAT FAR FROM
THE CAPITOL TO CENTRAL HIGH.
BUT THEY WERE STOPPED
TWO BLOCKS AWAY FROM THE SCHOOL
BY THE LITTLE ROCK POLICE
AND BY WATER HOSES
OF THE FIRE DEPARTMENT.
narrator: WITH THE OPENING
OF THE FOUR LITTLE ROCK
HIGH SCHOOLS IN AUGUST OF 1959,
WITH HALL AND CENTRAL
BOTH HAVING
AFRICAN-AMERICAN
STUDENTS ENROLLED,
THE CIVIL RIGHTS STRUGGLE
MOVED ON
TO OTHER CITIES
AND TOWNS ACROSS AMERICA.
>> AT THE TIME THAT LITTLE
ROCK'S SCHOOLS
WERE STILL CLOSED
IN THAT SPRING,
VIRGINIA SCHOOLS HAD OPENED--
THE CLOSED SCHOOLS IN VIRGINIA
HAD OPENED.
AND THE NEXT BATTLES
IN THE CIVIL RIGHTS MOVEMENT
IN SCHOOLS
WILL MOVE TO OTHER STATES.
AT LEAST THE FOCUS
WILL MOVE AWAY FROM ARKANSAS,
AND THEY WILL GO ON TO OTHER
CONFRONTATIONS IN OTHER STATES.
narrator: AND NOW,
50 YEARS LATER,
THE PEOPLE OF LITTLE ROCK
LOOK BACK
ON THOSE TUMULTUOUS TIMES
WITH SADNESS.
>> THE CRISIS MADE ME
SO MUCH MORE MINDFUL
OF OTHER PEOPLE AS HUMAN BEINGS.
>> THE CRISIS YEAR
IS A PUBLIC YEAR.
THERE ARE CHARACTERS--
IT'S LIKE A DRAMA
THERE ARE CHARACTERS
ON EITHER END OF THE SPECTRUM,
AND THE MEDIA AND THE PUBLICITY
GIVEN SHOWED EXTREMIST VIEWS.
AND IT WAS PLAYED OUT
ON A VERY PUBLIC STAGE,
BUT THE LOST YEAR
IS PLAYED OUT QUIETLY.
IT HAS PLAYED OUT
OVER LIFETIMES
IN THE PRIVATE LIVES
OF ALMOST 4,000 STUDENTS
AND THEIR FAMILIES.
AND IT HAS PLAYED OUT INTO
THE DECISIONS THAT THEY MAKE,
INTO THE ATTITUDES
THAT THEY HAVE.
THERE ARE STILL RACISTS LEFT.
THERE ARE RACIST PEOPLE
IN ARKANSAS AND ELSEWHERE
WHO HAD THIS EXPERIENCE.
BUT FAITH IN FELLOW MAN
TELLS ME THAT THE PEOPLE
WHO MAKE GOOD DECISIONS
AND RIGHT DECISIONS
CAN LEARN FROM IT
AND CAN GROW FROM THAT
AND CAN SHAPE THEIR CHILDREN
IN THAT WAY.
narrator: AFTER LEARNING
OF THE LOST YEAR,
PERHAPS THEY WILL HAVE
JUST A BIT OF PRIDE
FOR THE BRAVE PEOPLE
WHO STOOD UP
TO TURN THEIR COMMUNITY AROUND.
>> WHEN YOU GO TO THE HEART
AND SOUL OF THE COMMUNITY,
YOU GO TO ITS SCHOOLS.
AND WHEN THE SEGREGATIONISTS
TOOK THEIR STAND
AT THE SCHOOL DOOR,
I STILL WORRY
THAT THEY USED THE CHILDREN
TO MAKE THAT STAND.
>> WE ALL FELT
LIKE WE'D BEEN USED
AND THAT OUR SACRIFICE
IN THE NAME
OF INTEGRATION OR SEGREGATION,
WHICHEVER WAY,
HAS NOT BEEN RECOGNIZED.
>> I WOULD LOOK TO 1957, '58
AS ONE OF OUR SADDEST MOMENTS,
BUT I WOULD LOOK TO MAY OF 1959
AS AN EPIPHANY FOR A FEW PEOPLE,
FOR A MAJORITY OF THE PEOPLE
WHO WOULD GO TO THE POLLS
AND TAKE THE EFFORT TO VOTE.
I THINK THAT WAS
OUR SHINING MOMENT, ACTUALLY.
AND MOST PEOPLE
DON'T EVEN KNOW IT HAPPENED.
THE LOST YEAR IS SO IMPORTANT
TO LITTLE ROCK
BECAUSE THE YEAR BEFORE,
WE WERE BRANDED A CITY OF HATE.
BUT THE ELECTION OF MAY 25TH
SHOWED THAT LITTLE ROCK
COULD BE MOTIVATED
INTRINSICALLY.
THEY WERE NOT MOTIVATED
BY AN OUTSIDE COURT ORDER.
THEY WERE MOTIVATED FROM WITHIN
THAT PUBLIC EDUCATION
NEEDED TO GO FORWARD
AND THAT DESEGREGATION
COULD MOVE FORWARD
IN A GRADUAL
AND ACCEPTABLE FORM.
IT MAY HAVE BEEN
A STILL SMALL VOICE,
BUT IT WAS THE FIRST TIME
LITTLE ROCK FOUND ITS VOICE
AND TURNED ITSELF AROUND.
narrator: LIVES
WERE CHANGED FOREVER,
AND THE STORY OF THE LOST YEAR
WILL PERHAPS
BE REMEMBERED SOMEDAY
AS A BRIGHT SPOT
IN THE CIVIL RIGHTS STRUGGLE,
A STRUGGLE
THAT CONTINUES TO THIS DAY.
>> MY AUNT AND UNCLE
LEGALLY ADOPTED ME
SO I WAS ABLE TO GO TO SCHOOL
AT HOUSTON, TEXAS.
>> I WENT TO J.C. COOK
IN WRIGHTSVILLE, ARKANSAS,
THE SECOND SEMESTER
THAT SCHOOL YEAR.
>> SYLVAN HILLS.
THERE WAS ABOUT SIX OR EIGHT
OF US GOT IN A CAR ONE DAY
AND DROVE AROUND
UNTIL WE FOUND SOME SCHOOL
THAT WOULD LET US COME IN.
>> I WENT TO SCHOOL
ON TUESDAYS AND THURSDAYS
AND SHOT SNOOKER
AT THE POOL HALL IN CABOT,
MONDAYS, WEDNESDAYS,
AND FRIDAYS,
AND STILL PASSED.
>> I WENT TO SYLVAN HILLS
IN NORTH LITTLE ROCK.
>> I ATTENDED A HIGH SCHOOL
IN MISSOURI.
I LIVED WITH MY GRANDPARENTS
FOR ONE SEMESTER.
THEN I CAME BACK TO LITTLE ROCK
AND WENT ON TO COLLEGE.
>> THE LOST YEAR, I WENT
TO T.J. RANEY HIGH SCHOOL
WHICH WAS DOWN
AT 14TH AND CEDAR.
>> THE YEAR
THAT OUR SCHOOLS CLOSED,
I WENT TO KIRKWOOD HIGH SCHOOL
IN KIRKWOOD, MISSOURI.
>> IN 1958, '59,
I WAS LOCKED OUT OF HIGH SCHOOL,
AND I WENT TO SCHOOL
AT J.C. COOK
IN WRIGHTSVILLE, ARKANSAS.
>> AND I SPENT
MY SENIOR YEAR TUTORING
THE FOOTBALL TEAM
IN THE MORNINGS
AND BEING TUTORED MYSELF
IN THE AFTERNOONS.
>> MOST OF IT
AT JACKSONVILLE HIGH SCHOOL,
17 MILES NORTH OF LITTLE ROCK.
I DROVE UP
IN MY LITTLE BROWN FORD.
>> I HAD NO FAMILY IN
ANY OTHER PART OF THE COUNTRY,
SO I HAD NO PLACE TO CALL HOME,
SO I WENT TO WORK
AND TOOK COURSES AT NIGHT.
>> I WENT TO SCHOOL
AT SOUTHEAST HIGH SCHOOL
IN PINE BLUFF, ARKANSAS.
>> WE LEFT AND WENT TO MEMPHIS
TO SCHOOL
FOR ONE SEMESTER,
TO A PRIVATE SCHOOL THERE.
>> UNFORTUNATELY, I DIDN'T
GET INTO A SCHOOL THAT YEAR.
MY MOTHER WOULD PLAY THE RADIO
EVERY DAY,
HOPING THE SCHOOLS WOULD OPEN.
BUT THEY DIDN'T, SO SHE TOOK US
TO THE CATHOLIC SCHOOL,
BUT THE SISTER TOLD US THAT
SHE DIDN'T HAVE ANY MORE ROOM.
>> I WAS A CHEERLEADER
AT THAT TIME.
AND THEY HAD TOLD US
THAT IF THE SCHOOLS WERE--
THEY WEREN'T OPEN YET,
BUT IF WE WENT AWAY,
THEN WE COULD NOT CHEER.
>> THERE WERE MANY KIDS
WHO NEVER RETURNED
TO HORACE MANN HIGH.
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT
CENTRAL OR HALL.
Captioning byCaptionMax
www.captionmax.com